1974年纽约北部
UPSTATE NEW YORK 1974
<i>♪ Said the night wind to the little lamb ♪</i>
本字幕仅供学习，禁止私自压制散布
<i>♪ Do you see what I see? ♪</i>
别指望了
DON'T COUNT ON IT
萨德  我说爷爷家不许玩玩具。
Thad, I said no toys at Grandfather's.
但现在是圣诞节
But it's Christmas.
住手
Stop it!
-嘿  爸爸 -嘿
- Hey! Dad! - Hey!
萨德  你不能一直对别人哭诉
Thad, you can't go crying to other people all the time.
一个男人需要知道什么时候能自立
A man needs to know when to stand up for himself.
亲爱的着不是真正的魔法球
Dear Magic-isn't-real Ball,
他会成为一个男人吗？
will Thad ever be a man?
哎哟
Ouch.
前景不太好
Outlook not so good.
你弄坏了它
You broke it.
爸爸
Dad?
希德 希德
Sid Sid?
快来人帮帮我
Someone help me!
救命
Help!
你好
Hello?
泰迪斯·西瓦纳
Thaddeus Sivana.
你是谁
Who are you?
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
我是最后一个巫师领事
I am the last of the consul of wizards.
发誓要保护王国不受七宗罪的伤害
Sworn to protect realms from the Seven Deadly Sins.
多年过去了
For years have passed
我变得虚弱了
and I have grown weak.
这就是为什么我要找一个捍卫者继承了我的魔法
That is why I seek a champion to inherit my magic.
你想教我魔法吗？
You want me to do magic?
握住这个
With this,
我所有的力量都将是你的
all of my powers will become yours.
但首先
But first,
你必须证明你的心灵是纯洁的
you must demonstrate that you're pure of heart
和意志力坚强
and strong in spirit.
他撒谎
He lies.
别当他的捍卫者
Don't be his champion.
我们可以给你力量
We can give you power.
用眼睛去看
Search the eye.
你父亲认为你很软弱
Your father thinks you're weak.
向他展示你的力量
Show him your power.
不
No!
怎么搞的
What happened?
只有最纯洁的心才可以抵抗他们的诱惑
Only the purest of hearts can resist their temptations.
但是  你永远都不配拥有
But you, you will never be worthy.
你知道我知道什么吗  额
<i>♪ Do you know what I know? ♪</i>
等待
Wait.
我发誓  我告诉过你
I've telling you, I swear!
把我放回去
Put me back in!
-把我放回去 -撒德
- Put me back in! - Thad!
冷静
Calm down.
嘿  我要杀了你 你这个小混蛋
Hey! I'm gonna kill you, you little punk!
撒德…
Thad...
I.…我就在那里
I... I was just there.
这个人…是个巫师…
This man... this wizard...
他带我去了一座城堡…
He took me to a castle and...
住嘴 住嘴  住嘴！
Stop. Stop. Stop it!
你这个可怜的、爱发牢骚的小混蛋
You miserable, whiny, little shit!
你差点杀了我们！你知道吗？
You coulda killed us! Do you understand that?
国王对各地的人民说
♪ Said the king to the people everywhere ♪
听我说  额
♪ Listen to what I say! ♪
他会带我们来
♪ He will bring us ♪
上帝与光明  额
♪ Goodness and light! ♪
爸爸
Dad?
Dad!
爸爸
Dad?
你没事吧
You're okay.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
你做到了
You did this.
你看你干的
You did this!
不  爸爸…
No. Dad...
找到我们
FIND US
你的魔法变弱了
Your magic grows weak.
很快你就不能够控制我们了
Soon you won't be able to contain us.
咒语  寻找
Seeking spells!
找到一个值得我信任的灵魂！
Find me one soul who's worthy!
不管需要多长时间
No matter how long it takes.
雷霆沙赞
费城 现在
PHILADELPHIA PRESENT DAY
哦  这是真的
♪ Oh, it's the real thing ♪
嘿  额
♪ Hey! ♪
好啊  额
♪ Yeah! ♪
我一辈子都说我说过了
♪ All my life, I've said I've said it ♪
我会成为伟大的一员
♪ I'm gonna be one of the greats ♪
哦  这是真的
♪ Oh, it's the real thing ♪
我的天
Holy moley!
穿蓝色衣服的男孩
The boys in blue!
很高兴见到你
I'm sure glad to see you.
我一看到就打电话来
I called as soon as I saw.
他们在里面
They're in there.
你留在这里
You stay here.
警察
Police!
我看到他们藏在那里
I saw 'em hide back in there.
-警察  我们进来了 警察
- Police, comin' in! - Police!
-这里没有人  这是个壁橱  -你什么意思
- There's nobody here. It's a closet. - What do you mean?
你真的被贿赂了吗，恩？
You really bought that, huh?
哦  这是真的
<i>♪ Oh, it's the real thing ♪</i>
嘿  不  不  不
Hey, no, no, no!
停  停  停  停
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
马上打开  孩子
Open this up right now, kid!
你这是犯罪  孩子 你不能那样做
That's a federal offense, kid! You can't do that!
别上那辆车
Don't go in that car.
过来把门打开
Come on, open the door, please.
拜托  拜托  拜托
Please, please, come on!
快开门
Open this door, right now!
快点
Come on!
很好  很有趣
Very good, very funny.
非常有趣  那太好了
Very funny. That's great.
太好笑了  是的
That's hilarious, yeah.
呃  调度  我们需要支援
Uh, dispatch, we need backup
请到下一个购物中心
at the Lower One shopping center, please.
调度  取消那个请求
Dispatch, cancel that request.
有个孩子偷了我们的对讲机
Some kid stole our walkie-talkies.
对讲机：你多大了
<i>"Walkie-talkies"? How old are you?</i>
不  不  不  不 那是我的午餐  孩子
No, no, no, no. That's my lunch, kid!
巴森小姐  我  呃… 我一直在找你
Miss Batson, I, uh... I-I've been looking for you.
呃…不  天哪
Ugh... No. Gosh.
是我  是比利
It's me, it's Billy.
呃…可以
Ugh... okay.
我要老虎
I want the tiger.
我知道  亲爱的  我知道
I know, honey, I know.
但妈妈不是专业的
But Mom's not exactly going pro here.
我们射中一个了
We got one!
但我想要一只老虎
But I wanted a tiger!
哦  但这才是真正的奖品  宝贝
Oh, but this is the real prize, baby.
看到了吗
See?
你可以用一辈子
You can use that your whole life.
你总会找到自己的路
You'll always find your way.
我找不到路
I can't find my way.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom!
妈妈
嘿
Hey.
你和谁在一起  孩子
Who are you with, bud?
是的  他说是比利·巴森
Yeah, he says it's Billy Batson.
别担心  孩子
Don't worry, kid.
我相信她会来找的 没多久  好吗
I'm sure she'll come looking before too long, okay?
他们总是这样做
They always do.
妈妈  我回来了
Mom, I'm home.
来了
Yes?
嗯  嗯…
Yeah, uh...
这是瑞秋·巴森吗
Is this Rachel Batson?
谁在问
Who's asking?
嗯
Um...
是的  看  事情是…
Yeah, see, the thing is...
我想你是我妈妈
I think you're my mom.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
抱歉打扰你了
Sorry to bother you.
你只是想吃我的午餐，嗯？
You just had to take my lunch, huh?
你给我留了点薯条吗
You save me any fries?
匹兹堡的福斯特之家
Foster home in Pittsburgh
两周前报告你失踪了
reported you missing two weeks ago.
你送我回去
You sending me back?
不
No.
他们不想要你
They don't want you.
哼
Harsh.
你笑了
You laugh,
但你是从六个县外的寄养家庭里逃出来的  巴森先生
but you've run from foster homes in six counties, Mr. Batson.
来自好人的家庭… 谁想要你
From good people... who want you,
所有这一切都是为了寻找一个不存在的人。
all in pursuit of someone who arguably does not.
是时候面对面的
It's time someone looked you in the eye
然后直接告诉你
and told it to you straight.
我不需要继父母了
I don't need parents to play make-believe with.
我有一个妈妈
I got a mom.
对
Yes.
你是个侦探
You're some detective.
在28-40岁之间
between the ages of 28-40,
你把每一个都划掉了
and you've crossed out every one.
她还在外面
She's still out there.
我知道
I know it.
外面有一对夫妇 巴森先生
There's a couple outside, Mr. Batson.
他们想和你组成一个家庭
They run a group home.
我可以照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
要到你18岁的时候
When you're 18.
在那之前
Until then,
我不会让你住在街上
I won't have you living on the streets
找一个从未找过你的人
looking for someone who never looked for you.
给这些人一个机会
Give these people a chance.
因为这就是他们能给你的
'Cause that's what they're giving you.
你别无选择
You're out of options.
好吧  我们走吧
All right, let's get the spiel.
跟我和罗莎在一起  我们明白了
Just stay with me and Rosa, we get it.
我们以前也是被寄养的孩子
We were foster kids back in the day.
哦  回想起了以前的事情
Ooh, back in the dark ages.
女孩
Girl!
我内心年轻
I'm young at heart.
把我的手指放在脉搏上
Got my finger on the pulse.
是的  那是指他的血压  因为他老了
Yeah, that's a reference to his blood pressure because he's old.
比利  你对食物过敏吗
Billy, do you have any food allergies?
哦  希望你能做到  达拉在做饭。
Oh, wish you did. Darla's cookin'.
哦  盖瑞托  -什么
- Oy, guerito! - What?
我们知道这是多么的势不可挡
We know how overwhelming it can all be.
新房子  新面孔
New house, new faces.
都在你的脸上
All up in your face.
只是…以你自己的方式前行
Just... take it at your own speed.
你好
Hello?
我们回家了
We're home!
这就是你吃奶的时候会发生的事
That's what happens when you suck!
欢迎派对到此为止
So much for the welcome party.
是的  坐在沙发上的那人就是尤金
Yeah, that thing growing out of the couch would be Eugene.
是他吗
Is that him?
哦  天哪  比利
Oh, my gosh! Billy!
哇  慢点  慢点
Whoa, slow down, slow down!
欢迎回家
Welcome home!
-那就是达拉 我是达拉
- And that's Darla. - I'm Darla.
大拥抱
Big hugger.
我注意到了
I noticed.
死  死  死
Die! Die! Die!
他不是那个意思 这是游戏
He doesn't mean that. It's the game.
嘿
Hey.
天黑后不要苏打水  记得吗
No sodas after dark, remember?
哇  什么时候天黑了
Whoa. When did it get dark?
哦  海报  我给你做了一个  来看看
Oh, the poster. I made you one. Come look!
哦  不
Oh, no!
抱歉  一定是佩德罗在锻炼
Sorry, Pedro must've been working out.
他应该是 去上学
He was supposed to be at school.
哦
Oh.
在这里
Here.
对
Yes.
你们的数学系如此特别，这正是适合我的原因
Exactly why your Math Department is so uniquely suited for me.
我不能  我甚至不能…现在和尤金在一起
I can't, I can't even... with Eugene right now.
对不起的  玛丽  你好
Sorry. Mary. Hi.
大学面试
College interview.
我是比利 -我最兴奋的是什么
- I'm Billy. - What am I most excited about?
哦
Oh.
多好的问题啊 我希望你能问
What a great question. I was hoping you'd ask.
提到你是个寄养孩子，大学用餐
Mention you're a foster kid. Colleges eat that up.
我最兴奋的是
What I'm most excited about
是校园体验
is the campus experience.
作为一个寄养孩子 我是个大信徒
As a foster child, I'm a big believer
在寻找家庭和 最多的朋友
in finding family and friends in the most
不太可能的地方
unlikely of places.
哦  我会非常想念那个女孩的
Oh, I'm gonna miss that girl so much!
是加州理工学院 这是一所很有名望的学校
It's Caltech, it's a very prestigious school.
一路走来 在加利福尼亚
And also all the way in California.
但我们现在不必谈这个
But we don't have to talk about that right now.
这对我来说是个棘手的问题
It's a tough subject for me.
你喜欢素食吗
Do you like vegan food?
我喜欢动物
I love animals.
哦  不  托福
Oh, no! The tofurkey!
哦  不  我们可能要吃真正的火鸡了
Oh, no, we may have to eat a real turkey!
-是吗 -没关系  来  我带你去你的房间
- Is that? - It's okay. Come, I'll show you your room.
这有点疯狂 我知道  但是
It's a bit of a madhouse, I know, but,
真有趣
it's fun!
注意那里的颠簸
Watch the bumps there.
佩德罗  米阿莫  荷拉
Pedro, mi amor, hola.
向比利问好
Say hi to Billy.
不要把它当作个人问题  每个人都是这样
Don't take it personally. He's like that with everyone.
弗莱迪
Freddy.
这是比利·巴森
This is Billy Batson.
一定要让他觉得自己在家  好吗
Make sure you make him feel at home, okay?
尽量不要说太奇怪的话
Maybe don't say anything too weird?
哦  有件奇怪的事是
Oh, one weird thing is
你知道罗马人过去是用尿液刷牙的吗
you know the Romans used to brush their teeth with their urine?
显然  它起作用了
Apparently, it-it works.
是的  嗯…
Yup, um...
哦  是的  呃… 还有很长的路要走
Oh, it's, uh... it's a long way down.
相信我  我是凭经验说话的
Trust me, I speak from experience.
维克托推我
Victor pushed me.
它们看起来不错  但不买
They seem nice, but don't buy it.
这是真正的权力游戏
It gets real Game of Thrones around here.
什么
What?
老弟  我…只是随便说说
Dude, I'm... just messin' around.
嗯  我是晚期癌症  …
It's um, it's terminal cancer, I...
我只有三个月
I have three months.
开玩笑
Kidding, again!
你看我就像再说“为什么这么黑”
You look at me and you're, like, "Why so dark?"
你是一个残疾的寄养孩子  你一切都好    是吗
"You're a disabled foster kid, you've got it all." Right?
哦  是的  那是  呃  蝙蝠镖
Oh, yeah, that's the, uh, the old batarang.
我是说  这是复制品  但是…
I mean, it's a replica, but...
感觉像真的
Feel how sharp.
会在你睡觉的时候杀了你
Could kill you in your sleep with that thing.
你有过超能力的吗?
You ever a Supes guy?
是的  我也是
Yeah, me too.
看  圣杯
Behold, the holy grail.
一枚9毫米的子弹射中了超人本人
One nine millimeter round shot at Superman himself.
这是合法的
It's legit.
可能值得  我不知道 5-600美元  也许更多
Probably worth, I dunno, $5-600, maybe more.
包里有什么
What's in the bag?
嘿
Hey.
嘿  这都好  保持一定距离是好事
Hey, it's all good. It's good to maintain boundaries.
你不需要 说这么多  你知道的
You don't gotta talk so much, you know.
我是说  这个地方很棒 你会喜欢的
I mean, this place is great. You're gonna love it.
晚餐
Dinner!
全体船员
All hands on deck!
甜的
Sweet.
谢谢这个家庭
Thank you for this family.
感谢你今天的到来
Thank you for this day.
谢谢你的食物
Thank you for this food.
即使不是牛排里脊
Even if it's not steak fillet.
大学有2000名学生 ，你可能会这么想
Big school. 2,000 students, you might think,
哇  这么多陌生人
"Wow, so many strangers."
但如果你认为他们是
But not if you think of them as
对每个朋友来说都是可能的
possible for each friend then,
哦  这么多朋友
"Oh, so many friends."
校长  她的名字是 雪莉  她是最好的
The principal, her name's Shirley. She's the best.
下一个
Next.
这是我们的安全扫描仪
This is our security scanner.
就像在机场一样 这是完全安全的
Like in an airport. It's totally safe.
我知道是什么
I know what it is.
她总是这样吗
Does she always do this?
沉默使我不舒服
Silence makes me uncomfortable.
她几乎从不觉得不舒服
She's almost never uncomfortable.
祝你第一天愉快 大哥
Have a good first day, big brother.
听着  你没有 一直拥抱我
Look, you don't have to hug me all the time.
实际上我们不是 兄弟姐妹  所以
We're not actually brother and sister, so.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我-我不是故意让她…
I-I didn't mean to make her...
老实说  我实在是不知所措
<i>I was overwhelmed, honestly.</i>
他说我必须心地纯洁
<i>He said I must be pure of heart.</i>
他自称是巫师
<i>He called himself a wizard.</i>
就像…
<i>Just like a...</i>
一个来自哈利波特的巫师  一些…
<i>a wizard from Harry Potter, some...</i>
但你说的是另一个 有人经历过吗
<i>But y-you're saying that other people have experienced this?</i>
在某种意义上  是的
In a sense, yes.
你还记得吗 他对你说了什么
Do you remember what he said to you?
他测试了我
<i>He tested me.</i>
有些雕像
<i>There were these statues.</i>
他们的眼睛  就像 他们看着我
<i>Their eyes, it's like they were looking at me,</i>
让我思考问题
<i>making me think things.</i>
就像  可怕的事情
<i>Like, horrible things.</i>
这些和你看到的差不多吗
And do these approximate what you saw?
对 记忆里就是这样的
<i>Yes. That's exactly how I remember it.</i>
我-我不明白 你怎么知道…
<i>I-I don't understand. How do you know...?</i>
反复出现的图像 证明非常常见
Recurring imagery has proven very common
这种情况是集体癔症
in cases of mass hysteria.
集体癔症？
<i>"Mass hysteria"?</i>
我知道
I know.
这个词有点夸张
The term's a bit theatrical.
但以目击UFO为例
But take UFO sightings, for example.
飞碟就像天空中的灯
Lights in the sky, flying saucers.
都是彼此不认识的人的孤立事件…
Isolated incidents of people who do not know each other...
符号
Symbols.
问她有关符号的事
Ask her about the symbols.
对不起  关小姐
Sorry, Ms. Kwan.
但是作为一个例子 反复出现的图像
But as an example of recurring imagery,
也许你记得看到
maybe you recall seeing
在所谓的绑架之前有没有出现这些符号
these symbols before the alleged abduction?
不记得任何符号
<i>Don't remember any symbols, no.</i>
有件事我想我是在录像里看到的    嗯…
<i>I think I caught it on video. There was something, um...</i>
我记得我闹钟上的号码  它们一直在
<i>I remember the numbers on my alarm clock, they kept</i>
移位
<i>shifting.</i>
录像
Video?
给我看录像
Show me the video.
嗯  关女士 这是西瓦纳医生
Uh, Ms. Kwan, this is Dr. Sivana.
嗯  等一下  我可以传过去
<i>Um, one moment, I can send it.</i>
你好
<i>Hello?</i>
哦  天哪 谁在那儿
<i>Oh, my God! Who's there?</i>
你好
<i>Hello?</i>
发生什么事 发生什么事了
<i>What's going on? What's happening?</i>
我要走了 报警
<i>I'm-I'm going to call the police.</i>
我周围的一切都是耀眼的光芒
<i>Then this blinding light all around me.</i>
我觉得我是 被拉下来…
<i>And I felt like I was getting pulled down...</i>
像一座寺庙 在山上雕刻…
<i>Like a temple carved inside a mountain...</i>
正是你所期望的 自称是巫师的人
<i>Exactly what you'd expect from a guy who call himself a wizard.</i>
…带到那里拯救世界
<i>...brought there to save the world.</i>
西瓦纳博士
Dr. Sivana!
我理解你的激动
I appreciate your enthusiasm.
是你在资助我的项目
But you're funding my project.
但我在说话的时候不想被打断
And when I'm interviewing, I don't wanna be interrupted.
56人报告被绑架
56 reported abductions.
-我从没见过 -见过什么
- I never saw it. - Saw what?
博士  这是什么
Doctor, what is all this?
这些年来…
All these years...
我相信
I was convinced
我的顺序不对
I had the incorrect sequence.
或者…
Or perhaps...
打开门的符号错误
the wrong symbols to open the door.
但在那个女人的闹钟上
But on that woman's alarm clock,
七个符号
the seven symbols.
序列
The sequence
重复自身
repeating itself
七次
seven times.
这就是区别
That's the difference.
这是某种玩笑吗
Is this some sort of joke?
你可能觉得是这样
It may seem that way to you.
因为事实上我们不是
Because we're not, in actuality,
研究群体性癔症
studying mass hysteria.
所有这些人看到的
What all these people have seen,
他们每个人
every single one of them,
是绝对真实的
is absolutely real.
闹钟故障
An alarm clock malfunctions,
你的第一个想法是 这是巫师的证据
and your first thought is it's proof of a wizard?
来吧  西瓦纳医生
Come on, Dr. Sivana.
你不能相信 所有这些都是真实的
You can't believe any of this is real.
为什么  会这样
Why, yes.
是的  我知道
Yes, I do.
我一直在等你 此时此刻
I've been waiting for this moment
这么久了
for so long.
现在  我们到了
And now, here we are.
你不记得我了  是吗
You don't remember me, do you?
我记得你
I remember you.
你是那个男孩
You were a boy.
现在  你敢闯入我的王国里
Now, you dare intrude in my kingdom.
你知道这是什么感觉吗
Do you know what it's like for a child to be told,
你永远都不够好
"You'll never be good enough"?
不  你没有
No, you don't.
多年前你对我说的话
What you said to me all those years ago
让我意识到 我真的是谁
made me realize who I really was.
你知道吗
And you know something?
我不纯洁
I am not pure of heart.
巫师太软弱了  不能阻止我们
The wizard is too weak to stop us.
不
No.
No!
你没找到你的捍卫者
You never found your champion.
但我们找到了我们的
But we found ours.
你是真正的捍卫者
You are the true champion.
他们在利用你
They're using you.
对他们来说  你只是一种逃离这里的工具
You're nothing to them but a means of escape.
通过你  他们会把邪恶扩散到他们接触的每一个地方
Through you, they'll spread the poison to everything they touch!
让人类变成他们
Make mankind turn into them.
你寻求一个纯洁的灵魂  老人
You seek a pure soul, old man.
但没人符合
But no one's worthy.
飞行还是隐形
Flight or invisibility?
如果你有一个超能力
If you could have one superpower,
飞行或隐身 你会选什么
flight or invisibility, what would you pick?
每个人都选择飞行 你知道为什么吗
Everybody chooses flight. You know why?
这样他们就可以逃离这场对话了
So they can fly away from this conversation?
不  因为英雄会飞
No, 'cause heroes fly.
谁不想让人们 以为他们是英雄  对吧
Who doesn't want people to think they're a hero, right?
但是不可见  不可能 我是说  那太好了
But-But invisibility, no way, I mean, that's perfect.
四处监视那些 甚至不知道你在那里
Spying around on people who don't even know you're there.
到处偷偷摸摸
Sneaking around everywhere.
这完全是恶棍的力量  对吧
It's a total villain power, right?
然后他们做了这个研究 这是真的
Then they did this study, and this is a real thing.
他们问人们 同样的问题
They asked people the same question,
你知道  什么力量 你要吗  但这次
You know, what power do you want? But this time,
他们做到了 答案是匿名的
they made it so the answers were anonymous.
而且大多数人  自从 他们知道这是秘密
And-And most people, since they knew that it was secret,
说隐形
said invisibility.
我想那是 因为大多数人
And I think that's 'cause most people
不觉得自己是英雄 在内心深处
don't feel like heroes on the inside, deep down.
你要逃跑了
You're gonna run away.
我是说  你偷了我的超人子弹
I mean, you stole my Superman bullet.
伙计  我明白了  我明白了
Dude, I get it, I get it.
你被搞砸了 太多次了
You've been screwed over way too many times.
你不信任任何人
You don't trust anyone.
但这就是问题所在 关于隐身
But that's the thing about invisibility.
你自己处理
You handle it by yourself.
我没有偷你的哑弹
I didn't steal your dumb bullet.
嘿  今天怎么样
Hey, how was it today?
那很好  是吧
That good, huh?
哇
Whoa!
哦  天哪  弗莱迪
Oh, my God! Freddy!
你还好吗
You okay?
我勒个去
What the hell?
你们两个怎么了
What is wrong with you two?
-不可能会好起来的  -你要为此付出代价吗
- No way that's gonna buff out. - You gonna pay for that thing?
我差点把你的车撞出凹痕？
For the dent you made almost hitting me?
是的  当然  嗯  你们要的就是这些吗？
Yeah, sure, um, do you guys take these?
布雷特  住手
Brett, stop!
别碰我弟弟
Don't touch my brother!
什么  你需要你的假货家人支持你
What, you need your fake family to stand up for you?
-站起来  伙计 -是的  嗯
- Stand up for yourself, man. - Yeah, huh?
在这里  站起来 为自己站起来
Here, stand up. Stand up for yourself.
你打算怎么办 回家  对妈妈哭？
What are you gonna do? Go home, cry to mommy?
哦 对了  你没有妈妈
Oh, yeah, you don't have a mommy.
别伤害他
Stop hurting him!
嘿
Hey!
伙计  对不起
Man, sorry about that.
这不公平  但是
That wasn't fair, but,
再说一次  你不公平  所以
then again, you don't play fair, so.
退后  混蛋  我知道 如何使用这些东西
Back off, assbags, I know how to use these things!
哦
Oh!
嘿
Hey!
弗雷迪  你还好吗
Freddy, you okay?
你跑不掉的
Nowhere to run!
快快快 抓住他
- Go, go, go! - Grab him!
让开
Get out of the way!
哇
Whoa!
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no!
你死定了  孩子
You're dead, kid!
是的  你觉得你很有趣
Yeah, you think you're funny?
我知道你在哪儿上学
I know where you go to school, right!
下一站  30街车站
<i>Next stop, 30th Street Station.</i>
区域铁路线的变更
<i>Change for the Regional Rail Line.</i>
你好
Hello?
发生什么事
What's going on?
救命
Help!
天那
Holy moley.
你好
Hello?
什么东西
What the hell?
谁在那里
Who-Who's doing this?!
嗨  嗯…
Hi, um...
我以为 在30号街下的车
I was supposed to get off at 30th.
附带条件
比利 巴森
你怎么知道我的名字
How'd you know my name?
我是最后一个 巫师领事
I am the last of the consul of wizards.
永恒之石的守护者
Keeper of the Rock of Eternity.
哦
Oh.
你是
You're
那个家伙
that guy.
听着  我没有钱
Listen, I don't have any money.
别光看着我  孩子
Do not patronize me, boy!
你站在所有魔法的源头
You are standing in the source of all magic.
永恒之石
The Rock of Eternity.
七个敌人  七个巫师
Seven foes, seven wizards.
但是很久以前 我们选了一个捍卫者
But long ago, we chose a champion.
我们鲁莽地选择了
And we chose recklessly.
他用自己的力量复仇
He used his power for revenge.
把这七个致命的罪恶释放到世界上
Releasing the Seven Deadly Sins into the world.
数百万人丧生
Millions of lives were lost.
造成了整个文明消失
Entire civilizations erased from existence.
这就是为什么我发誓永不传授我魔法的原因
That is why I vowed never to pass on my magic
直到我找到一个 真正的好人
until I find one truly good person.
精神坚强
Strong in spirit.
纯洁的心
Pure in heart.
听着  伙计  也许这是魔法
Look, man, maybe this is magic.
我不知道  但是
I-I don't know, but,
你要找的人 好的  纯洁的人…
the people you're looking for, good, pure people...
我不是他们中的一个
I'm not one of them.
我不知道有没有人  真的
I-I don't know if anyone is, really.
你  比利·巴森  我只相信你
You, Billy Batson, are all I have.
全世界都是
All the world has.
把手放在这根棍子上
Lay your hands on this staff.
格罗斯
格罗斯.
说我的名字  就可以赋予你力量
And say my name so my powers may flow through you.
我向你敞开心扉  比利·巴森
I open my heart to you, Billy Batson.
这样做了后你就是捍卫者
And in so doing, choose you as champion.
谢谢  别冲我大喊大叫  先生  但是
Thanks. Don't scream at me, mister, but
我真的要走了
I really gotta get going.
我的兄弟姐妹被罪所杀
My brothers and sisters were slain by the sins.
他们的王座是空的
Their thrones lie empty!
我的魔法必须传承下去
My magic must be passed on.
现在
Now...
说出我的名字
Speak my name!
我-我不知道你的名字  先生
I-I don't know your name, sir.
我们刚刚见过面
We just met.
我的名字是
My name is...
沙赞
Shazam.
等等  真的吗
Wait, for real?
说吧 -好的
- Say it! - Okay.
天啊
Jeez.
我应该说吗
Should I say it?
像
Like,
沙赞
Shazam?
对
Yes!
带着我的名字
Carry my name
有了它  你就有了我所有的力量
and with it, you carry all of my powers.
所罗门的智慧
The wisdom of Solomon!
大力神的力量
The strength of Hercules!
阿特拉斯的耐力
The stamina of Atlas!
宙斯的力量
The power of Zeus!
阿基里斯的勇气
The courage of Achilles!
还有水星的速度
And speed of Mercury!
我怎么了 为什么我…
What happened to me? Why am I...?
你对我做了什么 你对我的声音做了什么
W-W-What did you do to me? What did you do to my voice?
你已经完全发挥了你的潜力  比利·巴森
You have been transformed to your full potential, Billy Batson.
用你的心 释放你最大的力量
With your heart, unlock your greatest power.
我们兄弟姐妹的王位在等着呢
The thrones of our brothers and sisters await!
呵呵  哦
Huh! Oh!
把我带出去
Get me outta here!
涂料
Dope!
我的兄弟 今天我为你的选择鼓掌
My brother, I applaud your choices today.
金鞋  金腰带 白斗篷
Gold shoes, gold belt, white cape!
它不应该起作用 但是  该死的  真的
It shouldn't work, but, hot damn, it does!
是的  警官  我知道 曾经就逃跑过  我…
Yes, officer, I'm aware he's run away in the past, I...
23次
23 times?
他没有网络社交账号
Guy's got no social media presence.
完全没有
At all.
那家伙是个幽灵
The guy's a ghost.
你们知道  伙计们 我很高兴去寻找比利
You know guys, I'm happy to look for Billy.
不仅仅是快乐
More than happy.
然后你要洗盘子 这才是最重要的
Then you gotta wash the dishes, that's what's more important.
你要怎么做  弗雷迪 跟他跑  哈哈哈
What are you gonna do, Freddy? Run after him? Ha-ha-ha!
很滑稽
Very funny!
不  等等  不要尖叫
No, wait, don't scream.
呃  维克托  维克托  维克托
Uh, Victor! Victor! Victor!
是我  是比利 是比利
It's me! It's Billy! It's Billy!
你问我 飞行还是隐身
You asked me, "Flight or invisibility?"
我觉得这很愚蠢 但现在我看起来像这样
I thought that was stupid, but now I look like this
我需要你的帮助
and I need your help!
熄灯后再过来见我
Meet me back here after lights out?
怎么了  巴德  你还好吧
What's up, bud? You all right?
是啊  是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
我只是…
I'm just...
我真的…悲伤
I'm really... sad.
因为比利走了
Because Billy's gone.
你知道
And you know,
也许是我的错 也许我做到了
maybe it's my fault. Maybe I did it.
呃  你知道  也许我打鼾
Uh, you know, maybe I-I snore.
嘿  嘿  嘿 不是你的错  孩子  好吗
Hey, hey, hey. Not your fault, son, all right?
我们会找到他的好吗？
We'll find him, 'ok?
你打呼噜没那么厉害
You don't snore that bad.
但你有点难闻
But you kinda smell.
哦  哦  哦  天哪
Oh, oh, oh, my God!
嘿  停在那儿
Hey, stop right there.
我怎么知道你不是 使用心灵感应能力的超级恶棍
How do I know you're not a supervillain using telepathic abilities
让我相信 你是比利  对吧
to make me believe that you're Billy, huh?
我要做的就是按这个拨号键
All I have to do is press dial on this thing.
不  不  我有证据 我有证据
No, no, I have proof, I have proof, here.
听着  我撒谎了  好吗 我拿了你的子弹
Look, I lied, okay? I took your bullet.
- Oop  不  不  不  不 -不  不
- Oop! No, no, no! No! - No! No!
愚蠢的成人的手
Stupid adult hands!
但你看到了 你看到了  对吧
But you saw it. You saw it, right?
看  弗莱迪 我发誓是我  好吗
Look, Freddy, I swear it's me, okay?
听着  我知道我们不是真的亲密、朋友或其他关系
Look, I know we're not really close friends or anything,
但你是我唯一熟悉的人
but you're the only person that I know
你知道什么关于斗篷十字军的事
that knows anything about this Caped Crusader stuff.
-那是蝙蝠侠 -什么
- That's Batman. - What?
算了吧
Forget it.
我可以吗
Can I...?
哦  是的  是的
Oh, yeah, yeah.
哦
Oh!
哦  天哪
Oh, my God!
太疯狂了  对吧
It's crazy, right?
你的超能力是什么
What are your superpowers?
超能力  伙计  我都不知道这是怎么回事
Superpowers? Dude, I don't even know how to pee in this thing!
好吧  你能飞吗
Okay, c-can you fly?
好吧  我们开始吧
Okay, let's do this.
我们该怎么做
How do we do this?
就像超人一样
Just, um, just like Superman it.
BIU
biu
显然  你必须跳起来
Obviously, you have to jump.
来吧
Come on.
这是怎么明显的
How is that even obvious?
好吧
Okay.
试着相信 你可以飞
Try, uh, t-to believe that you can fly.
好吧  我读过篇关于超能力研究的文章
Okay, I read this deep dive in the pyramid studies of superpowers
百分之六十的关键是信念
and in 6 out of 10, belief is the key.
信仰  信仰  信仰 好的  好的
Belief, belief, belief. Okay, okay.
我相信我能飞 我相信I.…
I believe I can fly. I believe I...
我相信我能飞
I believe I can fly.
附带条件
我  我   我
你相信吗
Did you believe?
是啊
Yeah.
你想试试隐形吗
You wanna try invisibility?
我该怎么办
How do I do...?
你…算了吧  你知道的 好吧  好吧  好吧
You... Forget it. You know. Okay, okay, okay.
哦  天哪  它奏效了
Oh, my God! It worked!
你去哪儿了
Where'd you go?
我就在这里 你看不见我
I'm right here. You can't see me?
在哪里
Where?
我是隐形人
I'm invisible!
我就在这里 我在这里
I'm right here. I'm over here.
我是隐形人
I'm invisible!
嘿  漂亮的装备  笨蛋
Hey! Nice outfit, dipshit!
我可能
I-I might have
在同时测试隐身能力和智力
been testing invisibility and super intelligence at the same time.
弗里曼  我要过来打败你
Freeman, I'm gonna come over there and beat you.
哦  天哪
Oh, my God!
闪电  它一直在我们眼前
The lightning, it was staring us right in the face the whole time!
显而易见的
Literally!
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
比利  我们得给你一个 闪电主题超级英雄的名字
Billy, we gotta give you a lightning-themed superhero name.
是啊
Yeah.
哦  对了
Oh, right.
嘿  你  回来…
Hey, you, back...
哦！
off.
超高速移动!
Hyperspeed, check!
我.…我很抱歉-我很抱歉
I... I'm sorry-I'm so sorry.
我以为是你在尖叫
I thought you were the one who was screaming.
我给他泼了胡椒喷雾
I doused him with pepper spray.
明智之举
Smart move.
是的  嘿  起来 抢劫犯先生
Yeah, hey, get up, mister mugger guy!
把钱包还给这位老太太
Give the old lady her purse back.
嗯  我和你一样大
Um, I'm your age.
他没有机会 因为我不让他拿走
And he didn't get a chance to take it 'cause I didn't let him take it.
很好  是的  很好 你真的很在行
Good, yeah, good. You're really on top of this stuff.
你应该教会其他那些老太太
And that should teach you that old ladies,
老太太喜欢自己动手
regular-aged ladies like yourself
不需要保护
don't need your protecting.
对吧？  所以接受惩罚吧  兄弟
Right? So get off, bro.
对不起  你是谁
I'm sorry, who are you?
他的名字叫雷鸣霹雳
His name is Thundercrack!
人们的英雄
Hero to the people.
集成电、力量和速度为一身的人
With the power and speed of lightning all in one.
伙计  那听起来像个屁股
Dude, that sounds like a butt thing.
-费拉德尔菲亚先生  -这是奶油奶酪的东西  伙计
- Mr. Philadelphia! - That's a cream cheese thing, dude!
超能男孩，是因为他拥有所有的力量
Powerboy, 'cause he's got all the powers.
因为有时候胡椒喷雾 无法抵御邪恶
'Cause sometimes pepper spray can't protect against evil.
神童  你认识这个孩子吗
Powerboy, do you know this child?
认识，认识一点点
Like, like a teeny little bit.
我真的不知道…
I don't really know...
是的  他就像我的经理  他就像一个小经理
Yeah, he's, like, my manager. He's like a miniature manager.
-我是他的经理 -嗯  你知道
- I'm his manager. - And uh, you know.
超能男孩也不工作  好吗  所以做点别的…
Powerboy's not gonna work either, okay? So work on something else...
嘿  嘿  嘿…
Hey, hey, hey...
闪电操纵 超高速移动  超强度的身体
Electricity manipulation, hyperspeed, super strength!
伙计  你太棒了
Dude, you're stacked!
你和超人一样酷 几乎
You're as cool as Superman! Almost.
我没看见你 或者这里发生了什么
I didn't see you or what's happened here.
我不想知道 别伤害我
I don't wanna know. Just don't hurt me.
-哦  不  不  我不会伤害你的 -感谢您的善举
- Oh, no, no, I'm not gonna hurt you. - Thank you for your kind donation.
不  不  不  但是如果你需要更多的帮助
No, no, no, but if you need any more help,
找一个仍然不能飞的超级英雄
just look for the superhero that still can't fly.
忘了飞行吧  伙计 我们刚赚了73块
Forget flying, man, we just made 73 bucks!
73块钱
73 bucks?
加油
Come on!
嘿  等一下
Hey, wait a minute.
我有个主意
I just got an idea.
我想买些你们最好的啤酒
I'd like to purchase some of your finest beer, please.
我不知道这件事  我是说  我们没有假身份证
I don't know about this. I mean, we don't have a fake ID.
弗雷迪  你能放松一下吗
Freddy, would you relax?
看我  我就是假身份证
Look at me, I am the fake ID.
登记簿上的所有东西  去吧  去吧
Everything from the register! Go! Go!
现在  快点
Now! Come on!
我时间不多 走吧  移动
I don't have much time! Let's go! Move!
我想要一切  快点
I want it all! Hurry!
这是你的机会
This is your chance.
哦 我.…可以
Oh! I... okay.
来吧  来吧  就是这样
Come on, come on, let's do this!
先生们
Gentlemen!
我们能不能像个真男人一样来处理这件事时  为什么要用枪呢
Why use guns when we can handle this like real men?
比利  小心
Billy, look out!
防弹的 你有防弹的能力
Bullet immunity. You have bullet immunity!
我是防弹的
I'm bulletproof.
今天是12月8日
Today is December 8th,
这是视频证明 真实性
and this is video proof of authenticity.
再开枪打死他
Shoot him again.
哦  是的  是的  是的 这里  这里
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Here, here.
你们两个走吧  进城去
Go, both of you, come on. Go to town.
等一下
等  等  等  等一下
我们还是不知道这套衣服 是否是防弹的
We still don't know if the suit is bulletproof or if you are.
开枪打他的脸
Shoot him in the face.
开枪打....我的脸？
Shoot me in the... in the face?
有点痒
It kinda tickles.
你们死定了
You're dead.
-对不起你的窗户 -祝你晚安
- Sorry about your window. - Have a good night.
但希望你不要再被抢劫
But you're welcome for not getting robbed!
快走
Come on!
我们走吧
Let's get outta here!
嘿
Hey.
-去对付坏人  -是的
- To fighting bad guys. - Yup.
尝起来像是真正的呕吐物
That tastes like actual vomit.
你知道的
You know,
哈巴内罗肉干  如果你吃够了
habanero jerky, if you eat enough of it,
它会在你胃里烧一个洞
it could burn a hole in your stomach.
-值得一干  -是的
- Worth it. - Yeah.
你的胃可能不会拥有超能力
Probably not you though. Probably got stomach superpowers.
可能
Probably.
哦  嘿  怎么了 我是个超级英雄
Oh, hey, what's up? I'm a superhero.
是的  他的名字是  呃
Yeah, his name is, uh,
闪光手指船长
Captain Sparkle Fingers.
不  不是  不  不是 这不是我的名字
No it's not. No it's not! It's not my name!
嘿  我们应该出去玩 我们就像  同龄人
Hey, we should hang out. We're like, the same age.
哦  不不  我要走了
Ho! po-po. I'm out.
嘿  等一下
Hey, wait up!
我的意思是  这是一个非常糟糕的想法
I mean, it's a pretty sick view.
我完全明白为什么洛基在这里生存会那么难
I totally get why Rocky was training so hard to get up here.
我喜欢你这样 这太酷了
I like you like this. This is so cool.
我的意思是  没有冒犯  但就像
I mean, no offense, but like,
一开始  你有点像
Like, at first, you were kinda like the opposite of how
达拉一样
of how Darla is.
迪克
A dick?
你说的  不是我
Your words, not mine.
但是  是的
But yeah.
好吧  好吧 我觉得每个罪犯
All right, well, I feel like every criminal
不是在吸毒 或者就是已经睡着了
was either on drugs or asleep by now.
想回家吗
Wanna head home?
像这样
Looking like this?
是啊  我是说
Yeah. I mean,
通常我们会有一个藏身处回去  但是
usually we'd have a lair to go back to, but
这是长期的
that's long term.
现在你有一张双层床
Right now you have a bunk bed.
我想到他只是害怕一个人
Just scares me thinking of him out there all alone.
这就是他所做的  罗莎
This is what he does, Rosa.
不同的是当他们找到他
Difference is when they find him,
我们会第一个带他回来的
we'll be the first to take him back.
张开双臂
With open arms.
两天都没来  连两天都没有
Didn't even make it two days. Not even two days.
宝贝  那时候我们逃跑了很多次
Baby, we did our fair share of running off back then.
至少  我做了
At least, I did.
甚至玛丽也做了两次
Even Mary did it, twice.
她第二次逃跑
That second time she ran off,
你说了什么 我永远不会忘记
you said something that I'll never forget.
你说
You said,
曾经这不是一个家  直到 你称呼他为它家
"It's not a home till you call it a home.
这是你的选择
"It's something you choose."
我们能做的就是 给他一个充满爱的地方
All we can do is give him a place full of love.
他是否选择 称之为家
Whether he chooses to call it a home,
这由他决定
that's up to him.
要帮我处理这棵树吗
Gonna help me with this tree?
这棵树太悲伤了
This tree's so sad.
你好
H-Hello?
我才从洗手间出来
Just got done in the bathroom.
哦  好吧  弗雷迪 亲爱的  晚安
Oh, okay, Freddy, sweetie, goodnight!
-夜晚 -夜晚
- Night. - Night.
弗雷迪  那是谁
Freddy, who was that?
是比利  他真的很累 他得了喉炎
It's Billy, he's just really tired and he has laryngitis.
-什么  喉炎 -我只是开玩笑  我只是开玩笑
- What? Laryngitis? - I'm just kidding! I'm just kidding.
他真的很累 想睡觉了再见
He's really, really tired and he wants to go beddy bye.
再见  什么是床铺再见 -藏起来  藏起来
- Beddy bye? What's beddy bye? - Just hide, hide.
比利  你回来了 让我们来看你
Billy, you're back! Let us see you!
我们很担心你
We're so worried about you.
我告诉过你这是个坏主意
I told you this was a bad idea!
弗莱迪
Freddy?
嘿  楼梯怎么了
Hey, what happened to the stairs?
嘿  遮住她的嘴 就像你要绑架她一样
Hey, covering her mouth like you're gonna kidnap her
让她 不那么害怕  好吗
is not gonna make her less scared, okay?
达拉  是我  是比利
Darla, it's me, it's Billy.
我知道我长得不像我 一个巫师让我看起来像这样
I know I don't look like me. A wizard made me look like this.
也许不要从巫师开始
Maybe don't start with wizard,
它只会使 她更困惑了
it's just gonna make her more confused.
一个老人带来的 我去寺庙
Some old guy brought me to a temple
他让我说  沙赞  …
and he made me say "Shazam"...
罗萨
Rosa!
你是用语言操控超能力
Verbally-triggered body manipulation properties!
你可以切换 说  沙赞
You can switch by saying "Shazam!"
宝贝  是你吗 你没事吧
Baby, was that you? Are you okay?
嗯
Um...
我在拧灯泡
I-I was screwing in a bulb.
听我说  达拉  你不能 告诉任何人这个  好吗
Listen to me, Darla. You cannot tell anybody about this, all right?
但是比利  他是个英雄
But it's Billy, he's a hero.
但是如果一个超级恶棍 发现他是个英雄
But if a supervillain finds out that he's a hero,
那会危及我们  好吗
that endangers us, okay?
英雄所爱的人就是 一个完美的坏人目标
A hero's loved ones are, like, a perfect bad guy target.
她好吗 在保守秘密
I-Is she good at keeping secrets?
一般般
Moderate.
-没有 哦  天哪
- No. - Oh, God.
好的  听我说
Okay, listen to me.
你不能告诉一个人 关于这个  好吗  拜托
You cannot tell a single soul about this all right? Please.
为什么  如果它是 我们信任的人
Why? What if it's people we trust?
因为好姐妹 不要泄露秘密
'Cause good sisters don't tell secrets.
-我是个好姐姐 -是的  你是
- I'm a good sister. - Yeah, you are.
你知道会怎样 你是个更好的姐姐
You know what would make you an even better sister?
是你帮我们修好门把手的时候
Is when you fix the- the doorknob for us.
甜美的梦
Sweet dreams.
好梦  晚安
Sweet dreams, goodnight.
晚安
Good night.
你好  先生  我能为您效劳吗
Hello, sir, how may I help you?
你好  先生
Hi, sir.
先生  你不能进去
Sir, you can't go in there.
请原谅我 你不能进去
Excuse me! You cannot go in there!
对不起  我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
萨德  这力只有董事会成员可以来
Thad, this is for board members only.
我知道  爸爸
I'm aware of that, Father.
现在
Now...
那天晚上  在车里…
That night, in the car...
我向你发誓 我看到了什么
I swore to you I saw something
但你从不相信我
but you never believed me.
我一直受到指责   不是吗
So much easier to blame me, wasn't it?
如果那天晚上我没有尖叫
And say that if I hadn't screamed that night,
你的腿还正常
you'd still have your legs.
好吧  现在  我有证据了
Well, now, I have proof.
够了  萨德
That's enough, Thad.
亲爱的Sid
Dear Sid.
你觉得呢
You think?
你知道的 甚至在事故发生之前
You know, even before the accident,
你轻视我
you belittled me.
别逼我扔你 离开这里  萨德
Don't make me throw you out of here, Thad.
你不需要制造场景
You don't need to make a scene.
哦  兄弟…
Oh, brother...
现场
The scene
才刚刚开始
has only just begun.
问问你能不能 把我扔出去
Ask that if you can throw me out.
什么
What?
问球你是否够男人 把我赶出这个房间
Ask the ball if you're man enough to throw me out of this room.
让我来帮你问
Let me spoil it for you.
看那…
Outlook...
不太好
not so good.
我在奉献的季节来到这里
I've come here during the season of giving
给你…
to give you...
你应得的
what you deserve.
哦  天哪
Oh, my God!
不  不
No! No!
不
No!
救命
Help!
谁来
Somebody!
救救我
Help me!
你不能一直对别人哭
You can't go crying to other people all the time.
什么罪最适合 你呢  父亲  恩？
What sin best befits you, Father? Hmm?
我什么都给你
I'll give you anything.
钱…
Money...
公司 你想要公司吗
The company? You want the company?
就在那里
There it is.
贪婪
Greed.
你真的认为
Do you honestly think
所有这些
all this
你积攒的财富
material you've accumulated
相当于实力
amounts to actual power?
这个…就是实力
This... is power.
比你以前更多
More than you ever had.
比任何人都多
More than anyone has.
还有一个更强大的
There is one more powerful.
巫师找到了他的捍卫者
The wizard found his champion.
杀死捍卫者
Kill the champion
在他熟悉他的全部能力前
before he learns his true potential.
否则他会打败你的
Or he will defeat you.
告诉我在哪里能找到他
Show me where to find him.
哦  贪婪…
Oh, Greed...
你可以抓住他
you can have him.
不
No.
No!
不
家庭不仅仅是一个词
<i>Family is more than just a word.</i>
这是一家人
<i>This is family.</i>
呃  布鲁克
Uh, Burke?
卡车在哪里
Where's the truck?
我听得见
I can hear it.
哦  天哪 -我的卡车
- Oh, my God! - My truck!
-我的卡车 -你在开玩笑吗
- My truck! - Are you kidding?
你们知道  伙计们…
You know, guys...
我觉得这车是修不好了
I don't think that's gonna buff out.
让残疾的孩子做肮脏的工作  哇
Making the cripple kid do the dirty work, wow.
我是个更好的演员  我可以扮演无辜的角色
I'm a better lookout. I can play innocent.
我不能
And I can't?
你的表情已经出卖了你
Your face gives off a very strong vibe
一个正在策划计划的人
of someone who's hatching schemes.
-我的脸  这张脸 -是的
- M-My face? This face? - Yeah!
可以
Okay.
你们有通行证吗
You boys got a hall pass?
哦  我们  是啊  总是
Oh, us? Yeah. Always.
你
You.
你看起来像 你在做什么
You look like you're up to somethin'.
我  有什么事吗 不  永远不会
Me? Up to something? No. Never.
我做不到什么事
I'm not up to something.
我们爸爸来接我们
Our dad's picking us up.
他  呃  他在… 企业
He, uh, he got held up at the... the business
办公室
office.
商务部  嗯
The business office, huh?
当然可以  孩子
Sure, kid.
看
Look.
父母或监护人 必须在身边
Parents or guardians must appear physically
检查学生
to check out students.
抓住了
Gotcha.
好吧  嗯 你听到了吗  爸爸
Okay, well, uh, you hear that, Dad?
-嘿 -沙赞
- Hey. - Shazam!
哦  嘿  孩子
Oh, hey, there, son!
哦  嘿  我还有一个孩子
Oh, hey, there, other son that I also have that's related
对，就是刚刚走过去那个
to that son I just passed in the hallway.
很抱歉我迟到了 我被耽搁了
I'm so sorry I'm late, I got held up
在商务办公室
at the business office.
做所有的工作
Doing all the work stuff.
这是所有孩子都非常敬佩的保安
This is the-the security guard all the kids admire so much.
哦
Oh.
那是另一个 这个很烂
That's the other one. This one sucks.
这      这并不好笑
This is... that's not funny.
对不起，我得和他谈谈
I gotta talk to him about that. I apologize.
不管怎样  这是我应该做的
Anyway, this is me appearing physically
让我儿子退学
to check my sons out of school.
所以  非常感谢你保证他们的安全
So, thank you so much for keeping them safe,
侦探莫兰
Detective Moron.
别阻止我
<i>♪ Don't stop me now ♪</i>
这是莫兰
It's Moran.
别阻止我
<i>♪ Don't stop me now ♪</i>
准备好了吗 代数
- Ready? - Algebra!
因为我玩得很开心
<i>♪ 'Cause I'm havin' a good time ♪</i>
科学
Science!
我是流星
<i>♪ I'm a shooting star ♪</i>
跃过天空 英语
<i>♪ Leaping through the sky ♪</i> English!
像老虎
<i>♪ Like a tiger ♪</i>
违抗重力定律 呵
<i>♪ Defying the laws of gravity ♪</i> Ho!
我是一辆经过的赛车
<i>♪ I'm a racing car passing by ♪</i>
像戈迪瓦夫人
<i>♪ Like Lady Godiva ♪</i>
我要走  走  走
<i>♪ I'm gonna go, go, go ♪</i>
没有什么能阻止我 强度试验1
<i>♪ There's no stopping me ♪</i> Strength Test 1
我在天空中燃烧  是的 哦
<i>♪ I'm burnin' through the sky, yeah ♪</i> Oh!
两百度
<i>♪ Two hundred degrees ♪</i>
所以他们叫我 华氏度先生
<i>♪ That's why they call me Mister Fahrenheit ♪</i>
我在旅行 以光速
<i>♪ I'm traveling at the speed of light ♪</i>
我想做超音速 你外面的男人
<i>♪ I wanna make a supersonic man out of you ♪</i>
飞行试验2
Flight Test 2
别阻止我
<i>♪ Don't stop me now ♪</i>
我玩得很开心
<i>♪ I'm having such a good time ♪</i>
我有个球
<i>♪ I'm havin' a ball ♪</i>
别阻止我 你还好吗
<i>♪ Don't stop me now ♪</i> You okay?
如果你想玩得开心
<i>♪ If you wanna have a good time ♪</i>
给我打个电话
<i>♪ Just give me a call ♪</i>
别阻止我
<i>♪ Don't stop me now ♪</i>
因为我玩得很开心
<i>♪ 'Cause I'm having a good time ♪</i>
我根本不想停下来
<i>♪ I don't want to stop at all ♪</i>
激光眼 试验1
Laser Eyes Test 1
我是火箭船 在我去火星的路上
<i>♪ I'm a rocket ship on my way to Mars ♪</i>
在碰撞过程中
<i>♪ On a collision course ♪</i>
我是卫星
<i>♪ I am a satellite ♪</i>
我失控了 传送测试1
<i>♪ I'm out of control ♪</i> Teleportation Test 1
我是性机器 准备重新加载
<i>♪ I am a sex machine ready to reload ♪</i>
像原子弹
<i>♪ Like an atom bomb ♪</i>
即将开始哦  哦  哦  哦 哦  爆炸了
<i>♪ About to oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, explode ♪</i>
我在天空中燃烧  是的
<i>♪ I'm burnin' through the sky, yeah ♪</i>
两百度
<i>♪ Two hundred degrees ♪</i>
所以他们叫我 华氏度先生
<i>♪ That's why they call me Mister Fahrenheit ♪</i>
我以光速旅行
<i>♪ I'm travelin' at the speed of light ♪</i>
我是如此…住手
I'm so... Stop!
我想做一个 你的超音速女人
<i>♪ I wanna make a supersonic woman of you ♪</i>
别阻止我  别阻止我 别阻止我
<i>♪ Don't stop me, don't stop me, don't stop me ♪</i>
嘿  嘿  嘿  额
<i>♪ Hey, hey, hey! ♪</i>
别阻止我  别阻止我 哦哦哦
<i>♪ Don't stop me, don't stop me Ooh ooh ooh ♪</i>
我喜欢
<i>♪ I like it ♪</i>
玩得开心  玩得开心
<i>♪ Have a good time, good time ♪</i>
别阻止我  别阻止我 哦哦哦
<i>♪ Don't stop me, don't stop me Ooh ooh ooh ♪</i>
嘿  嘿  嘿  额
<i>♪ Hey, hey, hey! ♪</i>
别阻止我  别阻止我 玩得开心  玩得开心
<i>♪ Don't stop me, don't stop me Have a good time, good time ♪</i>
别阻止我  别阻止我 哦  额
<i>♪ Don't stop me, don't stop me Oh! ♪</i>
比火车头更强大
More powerful than a locomotive.
陆冦玛 ？ 那是干什么？  一个古老的探索者
Locomo...? What are you? An old prospector?
能一跃跳过高楼
Can leap tall buildings in a single bound.
跳跃着跑
Single bound.
我很抱歉 对不起  伙计们  你好
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry, people! Hi!
您的手机已充电
Your phone's charged.
你知道吗 你需要一个口头禅
You know what? You really need like a,
就是你做了一件很酷的事后说的一句口头禅
like a mic-drop catchphrase after you do somethin' cool.
我一直在想这个
I've been thinkin' about that.
我在想  这个怎么样 那个怎么样
I was thinking, what about, what about this,
这就是为什么你不乱用电的原因
"That's why you don't mess with electricity."
显然  流行语不是 你的超能力之一
Catchphrases, obviously, aren't one of your superpowers.
你的手机已经充电了
And your phone's charged.
嗯  你认为 你能做得更好吗
Well, you think you could do better?
我勒个去
What the hell?
让它发光
Let there be light.
加油
Come on!
给我打个电话
<i>♪ Just give me a call ♪</i>
别阻止我
<i>♪ Don't stop me now ♪</i>
因为我玩得很开心
<i>♪ 'Cause I'm having a good time ♪</i>
我怎么办  不要介意
How do I? Never mind.
沙赞
Shazam!
我根本不想停下来
<i>♪ I don't want to stop at all ♪</i>
沙赞
Shazam!
好吧
<i>♪ Alright ♪</i>
你看到什么了  你看到了什么 有胸部吗
What'd you see? What'd you see? Were there boobies?
你看到乳头了吗
You see nipples?
你为什么不说话
Why aren't you talking?
我们需要更多的钱
We're gonna need more money.
哇  你在那里呆了五分钟
Wow, you were in there for, like, five minutes.
伙计  他们很有说服力
Dude, they were very convincing.
所以他们叫我 华氏度先生
<i>♪ That's why they call me Mister Fahrenheit ♪</i>
我以光速旅行
<i>♪ I'm travelin' at the speed of light ♪</i>
那是钱…很好  很好…
That's money... nice, nice...
走  走  走
Go, go, go.
如果你想玩得开心
<i>♪ If you wanna have a good time ♪</i>
不
No!
停下来  不
Stop, no!
-我都没看 -停下来  停下来
- I'm not even looking. - Stop. Stop.
我都没看
I'm not even looking.
哦
Oh!
-哦 击败了 -什么
- Oh, and done! - What?
击败了他
Finished him!
一个藏身处
A lair?
对
Yes.
显然 我们必须
And obviously, we're gonna have to be
进行此购买 匿名的
making this purchase anonymously.
很明显
Obviously.
嗯  如果你有位置
And um, if you have a location,
就像  在悬崖上  就像 城堡式的东西
like, on a cliff, like a castle-esque type thing.
俯视着水面
Overlooking some water.
在水上 海在它下面
Over some water, seas below it.
-很粗糙  你知道 -就像瀑布  所以你可以  就像…
- Rough, you know. - Like waterfall, so you can, like...
瀑布  是啊 如果有水…是啊
Waterfall! Yeah, if you have water... Yeah.
看  最大…大电压吗？
Look, Maximum... Voltage, is it?
你可以叫我马克斯
You can call me Max.
看 马克斯
Look, Max.
你为什么不
Why don't you just
从你要找多少间卧室开始
start with how many bedrooms you're looking for?
一 -七
- One. - Seven.
-一个 -七
- One? - Seven?
什么  我们现在还是寄养家庭吗？
What? Am I runnin' a foster home now?
看他扔的那个 足球进入太空
See the one where he throws the football into space?
所以涂料
So dope.
嘿  你们想知道谁在拍这些  对吗
Hey, you know, you guys gotta wonder who's filming those, right?
我的意思是  这本身就是勇气
I mean, that's bravery in and of itself.
我是说  是吗
I mean, is it though?
是的。我想说的是，也许要更加勇敢。
Yeah. I'd actually argue maybe even more brave.
拿着相机
Holding a camera?
在危险面前凝视
Staring in the face of danger.
像个古怪的粉丝
Like some weirdo fanboy.
嘿  弗里曼
Hey, Freeman.
如果我是你  我不会那样做
I-I wouldn't do that if I were you.
什么  你的朋友这次会用轮椅打我们吗
What, is your bestie gonna hit us with a wheelchair this time?
不  也许不是他  但书我的另一个好朋友会
No, maybe not him but I have another best friend.
他们会找到你并打到你们两个
Who might hunt you down and destroy both of you.
-好的  弗雷迪  -你可能听说过他
- Okay, Freddy. - You may have heard of him.
呃  呃  人类的动力风暴
Uh, uh, the Human Powerstorm.
频率弗林格  爵士-扎普斯-很多
Frequency Flinger, Sir-Zaps-A-Lot.
是的  他是个有很多名字的人
Yeah, he's a man of many names.
你知道红色气旋吗  你
You know the Red Cyclone? You?
呵呵  你知道什么
Huh. My ass, you do.
哦  我们比你想象的要知道得多
Oh, we're a lot closer than you think.
也许就在此刻
Maybe even at this very moment.
证明这一点
Prove it.
我明天就去  明天 他要来吃午饭…
I will tomorrow. Tomorrow he's gonna come to lunch and...
对  对吗  比利
R-Right, Billy?
哦  是的  然后是超人的
Oh, yeah, and then Superman's
会给我们带来甜点  对吧
gonna be bringing us dessert, right?
明天中午 你会看到的
Tomorrow, at lunch. You'll see.
当他不出现的时候
And when he doesn't show, then
我们要踢你的屁股
we'll kick your ass.
等等  我的身份是个秘密
So wait, my identity's a secret
所以我认识的人才不会受伤
so no one I know can get hurt.
除非这看起来很酷
Except when it makes you look cool, then
那就好了
then it's all good.
比利  他们不是超级坏蛋
Billy, it's not like they're supervillains
它们只是超级垃圾
they're just super douchebags.
所以你违反了自己的规则
So you're breaking your own rule?
知道了
Got it.
这东西和我的一样  也和你的一样
This thing is as much as mine as it is yours.
我开始觉得这都是你的事
I'm starting to think you think it's all your thing.
比利  不过你还是会这么做的  对吧
Billy, you're still gonna do it, though, right?
我是说  一个好兄弟会做什么
I mean, what would a good brother do?
全体船员
All hands on deck!
谢谢你的家人  感谢你今天的到来
Thank you for this family. Thank you for this day.
谢谢你的食物
Thank you for this food.
对不起  比利的手在闲着
Sorry Billy's hand's on vacay.
费城的大新闻 他们找到了一个穿着盛装的英雄
Big news in Philly. They found a costumed hero.
他做得很好
He's doing good.
是的  但他是吗
Yeah, but is he, though?
哦  难说
Oooh, controversy.
开始吧
Into it.
与我们分享你的观点  尤金
Share with us your perspective, Eugene.
只是说  他是什么  为什么给人们的手机充电
Just saying, he's what? Charging people's phones?
那又怎么样  我可以给电话充电… 用插头
So what? I can charge a phone... with a plug.
说教
Preach.
佩德罗  有什么想法吗
Pedro, any thoughts?
衣服很蠢
Costume's stupid?
大白斗篷  像是 结婚之类的
Big white cape like, he's getting married or something.
如果他的衣服没得选择怎么办
What if he didn't get to pick his costume?
有没有想过
Ever think about that?
你是个专家  弗雷迪 你怎么认为
You're a specialist, Freddy. What do you think?
是的  弗雷迪  让我们
Yeah, Freddy, let's
设法看到积极的一面
manage to see the positive.
好吧  好吧  我想 看起来像
Okay, well, I think it looks like
他对别人给他的东西没有感激之情
he doesn't have gratitude for what he's been given.
非常具体  好的
Very specific. All right.
也许对这个超级英雄来说
Maybe to this superhero,
感激并不意味着要随时在一起
gratitude doesn't mean having to be clingy.
随时在一起    哇 超趣的
"Clingy", wow, interesting take.
你知道  也许有时候超级英雄只是
You know, maybe sometimes a superhero just
想给我点时间
wants a little me time.
你知道  我的时间也可以理解为
You know, me time can also be construed as
离开他的家人
pushing away his family.
家庭  这就是他们现在的样子吗
Family. Is that what they are now?
这是超级英雄综合症的典型症状
It's a classic symptom of superhero syndrome
由德国心理学家创造
coined by German psychologist
海因里希·德冯… 德国的东西  哪里
Heinrich de Von... German something, where
超能力变成了一种麻醉剂
superpowers become an all-consuming narcotic.
儿子  我们还在吃晚饭
Son, we're still eating dinner.
他需要的是一个助手
What he needs is a sidekick.
说出一个很酷的搭档
Name one cool sidekick.
达拉  你为什么这么安静  宝贝
Darla, why are you so quiet over there, baby?
你从不失言的
You're never at a loss for words.
我在吃东西
I'm eating.
你为什么这样对我？
Why am I still doing this?
比利  你不能每天都逃避
Billy, you can't skip every day.
在你这个年纪
Not at your age.
我不再是你这个年纪的了
I'm not your age anymore.
但我可以和你一起去  我们只要
But I can go with you, we just gotta
把警卫骗出去 你知道  然后…
trick the guard out, you know, and then...
比利  你要去哪里
Billy, where are you going?
你还是会有 和我一起吃午饭  对吧
You're still gonna have lunch with me, right?
比利
Billy?
扎普斯先生  很多人还在自助餐厅吃饭等着  对吧
Sir-Zaps-A-Lot's still gonna eat in the cafeteria, right?
现在开始
<i>♪ Here we go now ♪</i>
如果你听到我说的话
<i>♪ Holla if ya hear me though ♪</i>
来感受我的流动
<i>♪ Come and feel me flow ♪</i>
好吧
All right!
你查过了吗
Did you check it?
人们通常会给我 一点钱  你知道  给…
People typically, like, give me a little money, you know, to...
你是一对甜蜜的夫妻 祝你你们今天过得愉快
You're a sweet couple, you guys have a good day.
哦  我的上帝
Oh, my God.
玛丽  玛丽  你还好吗
Mary, Mary, are you okay?
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
呃  我怎么知道 你的名字  呃…
Uh, how do I know your name, uh...
呃  我的超能力之一 就是能知道你名字
Uh, one of my superpowers is name-guessing.
我敢打赌  这真的很奇怪
Which is really weird, I bet.
呃  它不像超级力量或超级速度那么酷
Uh, it's not as cool as super strength or super speed
但当我遇到新朋友时  这真的很有帮助
but it's really helpful when I meet new people.
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
不  我…我没事
No, I'm... I'm okay.
谢谢  嗯…
Thank you, um...
我只需要一秒钟来思考
I just need a second to think.
今天真是奇怪
This has been such a weird day.
嗯  利用我的观察超能力
Um, using my powers of super observation,
我看到你拿着 大学的信
I see that you're holding a letter from a college
在你手中  你不高兴是因为你没被录取
in your hand. Are you upset because you didn't get in?
我被录取了
I got in.
休斯敦大学      好吧  现在我的超能力让我很失望
Uh... well, now my superpowers are failing me
我很困惑
and I'm very confused.
是的  我也是
Yeah, me too.
我不知道  我知道我应该高兴因为这是我的梦想
I don't know. I know I should be excited 'cause this is my dream
我为此付出了很大的努力
and I worked really, really hard for this.
但就像…
But it's like...
我不知道  离开我的家人这会很难过  你知道吗
I don't know, leaving my family does not feel fun, you know?
我能给你一点建议吗
Can I-Can I-Can I give you a little piece of advice?
别担心 其他人
Don't be worried about everybody else.
一定要注意的第一条
Always look out for number one.
-甘地说过 -我不认为他这么说
- Gandhi said that. - I don't think he said that.
是的  他做到了 -甘地没有这么说
- Yeah, he did. - Gandhi did not say that.
-像甘地这样的人说过 -照顾好第一个
- Somebody like Gandhi said that. - Take care of number one?
这是真的…也可能是尤达
It was a really wi... It might have been Yoda.
听 -对不起  不
- Listen. - I'm sorry, no.
同意不同意 重点是…
Agree to disagree. The point is...
你知道吗  你得小心点
You do you, you know? You gotta look out for you.
尽可能远离这个地方
And get as far away from this place as you can.
我不知道我是否愿意
I don't know if I want to.
当然了 你打算怎么办
Of course you do. What are you gonna do?
你打算在一个集体家庭里度过余生？
You're gonna live in a group home for the rest of your life?
看  家庭是为那些不能照顾自己的人准备的
Look, families are for people who can't take care of themselves.
好吗？  所以
Okay? So.
你知道  你可以 照顾好你自己
And you know, y-you can take care of yourself, you know.
另外   过马路时看两边
Also, look both ways when you cross the street.
我就打电话给他
I'll just call him.
电话响了
It's ringing.
红色旋风  嘿 嘿  怎么了
Red Cyclone! Hey! Hey, what's goin' on?
哦  太疯狂了 是的  顺便说一下  我是弗雷迪
Oh, that's crazy. Yeah, it's Freddy, by the way.
是啊  太疯狂了 那是…
Yeah, it's crazy. That is...
伟大的故事
Great story.
他没说话
He's not talking.
我是  我是
I was! I was!
我们是朋友 我认识他  我愿意
We're friends. I know him. I do.
我知道      我知道
I know... I know...
倒霉
Shit.
来吧  现在
Come on, now.
举起手来  用我的手闪电  额
♪ Hands. Lightning with my hands. ♪
用我的手闪电  额
♪ Lightning with my hands. ♪
嘿  嘿
Hey! Hey!
嘿  小伙子
Hey, young man.
哇  哇  哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
我现在正在表演节目
I'm in the middle of a show right now.
我该怎么帮你
How can I help you?
我只想说谢谢你今天没来吃午饭
I just wanna say thank you for showing up to lunch today.
是的  我有个小东西叫手提箱  对吧
Yeah, I got a little something called a suitcase wedgie, right?
我不知道你是否曾经 听说过  但现在
I don't know if you've ever heard of it, but it's when
有人像那样抓你的内裤
someone grabs your underwear like that
像手提箱一样抱着你
and hold you like a suitcase,
带你走过走廊
walks you down the hallway.
这是我的内裤
And this was my underwear.
格罗斯
Gross
你说过你会来的
You said you'd come.
你说我会来  我从没说过我…
You said I will come, I never said I was...
我是个超级英雄  伙计
I'm a superhero, dude.
好吧  你表现得很英勇
Well, you're acting real heroic.
今天人们给你多少钱
How much are people paying you today?
听着  我现在有很重要的事  好吗
Listen, I have serious responsibilities now, okay?
但那很酷  因为我可以用我的…
But that's cool because I can carry that burden with my...
举起手来  用我的手闪电  额
♪ hands. Lightning with my hands. ♪
我的天
Holy moley.
别动
Don't move!
大家不要动
Nobody move!
哦  不
Oh, no.
不  不  不  不  不 停下来 停下来
No, no, no, no, no. Stay, stay.
停下来  停下来  停下来
Stay. Stay. Stay.
哦
Oh.
哦  看起来很疼
Oh, that looked like it hurts.
是他
It's him!
是超级英雄
It's the superhero guy!
救救我们
Save us!
来吧
Come on.
来吧…
Come...
他在干什么 发生什么事
What's he doing? What's going on?
什么
What?
哦  不  哦  不  不 请不要逼我这么做
Oh, no. Oh, no, no. Please don't make me do this.
这是有史以来最糟糕的主意
That is the worst idea ever!
哦  哦  我做到了
Oho! Oh, I did it!
我做到了
I did it!
我赶上公共汽车了 我赶上了公共汽车
I got the bus! I got the bus.
没人进去
Nobody move in there!
我得把这东西放下 我得把这东西放下
I gotta put this thing down, I gotta put this thing down.
不  不  不  小狗  小狗 你得走了  移动
No, no, no, doggie, doggie, you have to move. Move!
嘘  嘘
Shoo! Shoo!
请做一只好狗 好狗
Please be a good dog. Good dog!
哦  你真是个坏狗
Ooh, you're being a bad dog.
去吧  去吧
Go! Go!
请走  请挪动一下
Please go. Please move.
是的  谢谢 谢谢您  谢谢您
Yes, thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢您
Thank you.
是啊
Yeah.
是的  不  不  不  我的朋友…
Yeah, no, no, no, my f...
我在附近 你知道  所以我想…
I was in the neighborhood, you know, so I thought...
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
你知道  反正这是我的错
You know, it's kinda my fault, anyway.
所以  费城似乎提前得到了一份圣诞礼物
So, it seems Philadelphia has gotten an early Christmas present
以超级英雄的形式出现
in the form of its very own superhero.
我们出去了
And we're out.
-嘿  非常感谢 -哦  当然  是的
- Hey, thank you very much. - Oh, of course, yeah.
伙计   伙计   伙计  你看到了吗
Dude! Dude, dude! Dude, did you see that?
是的  你电坏了一辆公共汽车还差点杀了这些人
Yeah, you electrocuted a bus and almost killed these people.
然后我接住了
And then I caught it!
弗莱迪  我徒手接住了一辆公共汽车  伙计
Freddy! I caught a bus with my bare hands, man!
我像抓飞球一样抓住公共汽车就  就像…
I caught a bus like people catch fly balls, like...
那是谁干的  我做到了
Who does that? I do that.
比利  你什么都做不了  你…
Billy, you do nothing, you...
你自私自利  让别人付钱给你
you take selfies and make people pay you.
你知道吗  算了吧
You know what, forget it.
当你看起来像这样的时候  我真的不能和你说话
I can't really talk to you when you look like this.
你只希望是你
You just wish it was you.
不，狗屎
No shit.
你觉得呢
You think?
我会为了保护拥护你的人而杀人
I would kill to have what you have.
因为我做的每件事
'Cause everything I do
就像是某种绝望的尝试
is like, some-some desperate attempt
让人们注意到我
to get people to notice me.
不为我难过
To not feel sorry for me.
我是说  看看我 看着我
I mean, look at me. Look at me.
你看见我了吗
Do you even see me?
因为大多数人没有
'Cause most people don't.
因为他们不想
'Cause they don't want to.
你也没有
And you don't either.
我是说  你认为 这就是你
I mean, you think this is who you are?
我是说  比利  你才14岁
I mean, Billy, you're 14.
现在你也不比布雷耶强了
And now you're no better than the Breyers.
所有这些力量
All this power,
你所做的一切都变成了一场炫耀
and all you did was turn into a showoff and a bully.
无论如何  孩子
Whatever, kid.
我做我想做的
I do what I want!
我大概20多岁
And I'm like mid-20s, probably.
甚至  比如  30岁
Maybe even, like, 30.
选择一个
Chosen one.
所谓的完美男人
The so-called perfect man.
纯真的心
Pure of heart.
各方面都完美无瑕
Flawless in every way.
是什么让你这么有价值
What made you so worthy?
对不起  我能帮忙吗… 我能帮忙吗
I'm sorry, can I help... can I help...?
你要签名吗 或者是什么
D'you want a autograph or somethin'?
给我你的力量
Give me your power.
或死亡
Or die.
哦  快点
Oh, snap.
你像个坏人  对吧
You're like a bad guy, right?
好的  好的  好的  好的
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
听着  在这之前 你真傻
Look, before this gets really stupid for you,
你应该知道 我基本上是不可战胜的
you should know that I'm basically invincible.
人类的武器不嗜血
The weapons of man draw no blood from our kind.
这是……
This is the...
唯一的事情就是 消灭魔法
The only thing that extinguishes magic
是魔法
is magic.
是时候把你的力量交给我了
Time to transfer your power to me.
哦  爷爷  你没看见这个吗？
Oho, you did not see that one coming, did you, grandpa?
这是他们的街头规则
Them's street rules!
好的  好的  好的  好的  好的
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay!
对不起  对不起  对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
我不应该像那样把你打得落花流水
I never should've punched you in the nuts like that.
那完全是我的错
That was totally my bad.
我们可以谈谈这个
We can talk about this.
你像个孩子一样卑躬屈膝
You grovel like a child.
那是因为我是一个 我是个孩子
That's because I am one. I-I'm a kid.
你不想 伤害一个孩子  是吗
You don't want to hurt a kid, do you?
我相信我能飞
I believe I can fly!
我相信我能飞 我会飞
I believe I can fly! I can fly!
弗雷迪说如果我相信 我会飞
Freddy said if I believe, I can fly!
那我就可以飞了  所以我相信
Then I can fly, so I believe!
我相信  哦  拜托
I believe, oh, please!
可以  超人
Okay! Superman!
超人 这是什么手臂
Superman! What arm is it?!
为什么我不飞
Why am I not flying?!
拜托  我不想死
Please, I don't wanna die!
哦
Oh.
哇
Whoa.
我在漂浮
I'm floating!
我会飞
I can fly!
比利
Billy?
弗莱迪  我需要你的帮助
Freddy! I need your help!
你会飞吗
You can fly?
另一个人是谁
Who's the other guy?
圣诞老人
Santa!
所以  你和克劳斯太太在夏天做什么
So, like, what you and Mrs. Claus do in the summertime?
嗯  在某些方面
Well, in some ways,
圣诞老人总是在这儿等你
Santa's always here for you.
哦  救命啊
Oh, help!
救救圣诞老人
Help Santa!
圣诞老人需要帮助
Santa needs help!
如果你需要我们  请大声喊一声
Give us a shout if you need us.
我只是想在这里冷静一下 一会儿  如果可以的话
I'm just gonna chill in here for a little while, if that's okay.
这太疯狂了
This is crazy!
这太疯狂了  你不必和这家伙打
This is crazy. You don't have to fight this guy.
这不是你的工作 你可以跑  对吧
This isn't your job. You can run, right?
对  你可以跑  令人惊叹的
Yes! You can run. Awesome.
回来
Get back!
只要…走开
Just get... Get away!
我是蝙蝠侠 抓住他  蝙蝠侠
<i>I'm Batman.</i> Get him, Batman!
快点
Come on!
沙.…沙赞
Sh... Shazam!
比利
Billy!
比利  你在哪里
Billy, where are you?
比利
Billy!
你在哪里  比利
Where are you, Billy?
比利  快点
Billy, come on!
比利
Billy.
-他在哪里 -嗯  超级恶棍
- Where is he? - Um, supervillain.
超级恶棍  超级恶棍
Supervillain! Supervillain!
更糟
Worse.
更糟糕
Much worse.
放射性拟人
Radioactive anthromorph.
精神能量操纵者
Psychic energy manipulator.
我不会让你读懂我的心思的
I won't let you read my mind.
我脑子一片空白 你不能进去
My mind is blank. You can't get in.
我不需要读懂你的心思
I don't need to read your mind.
因为你要告诉我
Because you are going to tell me.
他在哪里
Where is he?
哦  天哪  你没事吧
Oh, my God, are you okay?
你还好吗
You okay?
怎么搞的 你受伤了吗
What happened? Are you hurt?
进来吧
Come inside.
我们需要谈谈
We need to have a talk.
只是不要对他太很严厉  好吗
Just don't be too hard on him, okay?
跑出去追我们  说谎
Running out on us. Lying.
然后我接到一个电话 来自学校
Then I get a call from the school
告诉我你一直在逃课
telling me you've been cutting class.
打架
Getting in fights.
哇  那是…
Whoa, is that...?
弗雷迪在干什么 和超级英雄在一起
What's Freddy doing with a superhero?
这个超级英雄是什么 和弗雷迪在一起
What's this superhero doing with Freddy?
你记得晚餐吗
You remember dinner?
当比利和 弗雷迪在争论
When Billy and Freddy were arguing
的时候像这两个人吗？
like an old married couple like this?
当他救我的时候  他知道我住在一个寄养家庭里
When he rescued me, he knew I lived in a group home.
他知道我的名字 他叫我玛丽
He knew my name. He called me Mary.
等待
Wait.
你是说比利是超级英雄？
Are you saying Billy's the Human Powerstorm?
对  你们搞清楚了
Yes! You guys figured it out!
全靠你们自己  我没有帮助
All on your own. I didn't help.
我没有违背任何承诺
I didn't break any promises.
你知道吗
You knew?
我是个好姐姐
I'm a good sister!
我是说  你在想什么
I mean, what were you thinking?
然后你把弗雷迪带进去
Then you bring Freddy into it.
给他点空间  伙计们 他有点心烦意乱  可以吗？
Give him some space, guys. He's a little upset. Okay?
比利
Billy?
你就是他
You're him.
你是英雄
You're the hero.
是的  好吧  不再是了  所以
Yeah, well, not anymore, so.
你为什么有我的笔记本
Why do you have my notebook?
尤金完成了你的搜索
Eugene finished you search.
听着  我不是黑客  好吗
Look, I'm not a hacker, okay?
但我玩了看门狗和Uplink.
But I have played Watchdogs and Uplink.
也许我学到了一些技巧
And maybe I did pick up a few skills
这技巧让我进入了联邦数据库
which maybe did get me into federal databases
大多数人不能进入  但是…
most people can't get into, but...
真为你高兴 但我要走了
Good for you, but I'm gonna go.
你父母的名字 是玛丽莲和C.C.巴森
Your parents' names are Marilyn and C.C. Batson.
什么
What?
你出生于 明尼苏达州祖布罗塔
You were born in Zumbrota, Minnesota.
他们离婚的时候 你三岁
They divorced when you were three.
你妈妈那年搬来的
Your mom moved here that year.
20个月后  你迷路了
20 months later, you got lost.
你没找到他们是因为 你爸爸在监狱里
You never found them 'cause your dad's been in prison
在佛罗里达呆了10年
in Florida for 10 years.
你妈妈…
And your mom's...
什么
What?
她死了吗
Is she dead?
她在两个地铁站外
She's two subway stops away.
什么
What?
你知道  你没找到她
You know, you didn't find her
因为她改回了她结婚前的姓
because she reverted to her maiden name.
嘿  比利  比利
Hey, Billy! Billy!
维克多  拿钥匙
Victor, get the keys.
孩子们  呆在这里 以防比利回来
Kids, stay here, in case Billy comes back.
进去  走吧
Get inside. Let's go.
等等  我以为我们是要去追比利
Wait. I thought we were running after Billy?
不  我们现在就在这儿等
No, we're gonna wait here for now.
比利
Billy?
弗莱迪
Freddy?
哦  多么离奇
Oh, how quaint.
实际上  我收回那句话
Actually, I take that back.
多糟糕的事啊
What a shithole.
就一秒钟
Just a second.
嘿  听着  我上班已经迟到了  好吗
Hey, look, I'm late for work already, all right?
我们不需要任何 杂志之类的
We don't need any magazines or whatever.
哦  我不是
Oh, I'm not.
你可能不认识我  但是
You probably don't recognize me, but
我找到回家的路了
I found my way home.
妈妈
Mom.
是我
It's me.
哦  天哪
Oh, God.
它是
Is it?
嗯  等等
Um, hang on.
谁在门口
Who's at the door?
这是…
It's um...
没人  特拉维斯
It's no one, Travis.
那不是爸爸  是吗
That wasn't Dad, was it?
不 我.
No, I...
听着  嗯…
Listen, it's um...
是你吗
It's really you, huh?
我不是想逃避
I didn't mean to run away.
你知道吗
You know that, right?
这件事过去了 这只是偶然的事  我…
I let go but it was by accident, I...
是的  我知道  我知道
Yeah, I know, I know.
我看见你了
I saw you.
什么
What?
之后我看见你了
I saw you after.
所以  这绝不是你的错
So, it was never your fault.
我17岁
I was 17.
还有我爸爸  他把我踢了出去
And my dad, he kicked me out.
你爸爸只是…
And your dad just...
决定不参与任何事情
decided not to be a part of anything.
我受伤了 我被抛弃了
And I was hurting and I was screwed up.
我想要那只老虎
I wanted the tiger.
我知道  我知道  亲爱的  但是
I know, I know, honey, but
妈妈不是很专业  好吗
Mom's not exactly going pro here, okay?
比利
Billy?
Billy!
比利
天哪  比利 这不好笑
Jesus Christ, Billy, this isn't funny!
给你  伙计
Here you go, buddy.
最后一次 我看见你和警察在一起
But it's just once I saw you with the police,
我意识到
I realized that
他们能比我更好地照顾你
they could do a better job taking care of you than I ever will.
但你很好  对吧
But you're good, right?
我是说你成长起来了
I mean you landed on your feet.
因为  我是说  你看起来很好
'Cause, I mean, you look real good.
只是…
It's just...
比利  现在对我来说不是什么好事情
Now is not a really good time for me, Billy.
我只想
All I wanted to do was
告诉你我过得很好  但是…
let you know I'm doing good, but...
我必须回到真正属于我的家了  所以
I have to get back to my real family, so.
这个
Here.
这是什么
What's this?
玛丽莲  外面发生什么事了
Marilyn! What's going on out there?
你可能比我更需要它
You might need it more than me.
弗雷迪  你说得对  对不起  我对你大喊大叫
Freddy, you were right. Sorry I yelled at you.
回来吧  比利
<i>Come home, Billy.</i>
回家吧
<i>Come home.</i>
比利  超级恶棍 超级恶棍
<i>Billy! Supervillain! Supervillain!</i>
沙赞
Shazam!
你是谁 你想要什么
Who are you? What do you want?
我想要什么
What do I want?
我想要…
I want...
他
That.
哇
Whoa.
踢他的屁股  比利
Kick his ass, Billy!
哦  天哪
Oh, God.
是的  比利
Yes, Billy.
无论如何  试试看
Try it, by all means.
放开他们  我就进去
Let them go and I'll come inside.
哦  你先进来
Oh, first you come inside,
也许我会放了他们
then maybe I'll let them go.
好孩子
Good boy.
因为你就是这样  不是吗
'Cause that's all you are, isn't it?
你多大了
How old are you?
-基本上  15 -嗯
- Basically, 15. - Hmm.
当我还是个孩子的时候
When I was a child,
老人告诉我 我不够好
the old man told me I wasn't good enough.
给你
And here you are,
懦夫
a coward.
离开我
Run from me?
那个巫师选择了你  你不是英雄
And that wizard chooses you. You're not a hero.
但我会给你一个机会
But I'm gonna give you the opportunity to be one.
给我力量 捍卫者的
Give me the power of a champion.
不  别这样  比利
No, don't do it, Billy!
给我力量
Give me the power
我会让他们走的
and I'll let them go.
达拉  没有
Darla, no.
别  别走  比利
Don't, don't go, Billy!
别走  别走  比利
Don't go! Don't go, Billy!
不  不  我-我必须 我必须  这是…
No, no, I-I have to, I have to, it's...
好弟弟都会这么做的  对吧
It's what a good brother would do, right?
比利
Billy.
我把我的一生都献给了来到这里
I dedicated my life to getting here.
我扫荡了大地
I scoured the earth.
没有人相信我
No one believed me.
没人帮忙
No one helped.
不是巫师
Not the wizard.
不是我的家人
Not my family.
我只有自己
I only had myself.
我明白了
I get it.
I get what that's like.
感觉自己是世界上唯一的一个人
Feeling like you're all alone in the world.
站起来
Stand.
感觉只有一件事  如果你能找到的话
Feeling like there's that one thing, if you could just find it.
那你就足够好了
Then you'd finally be good enough.
站起来
Stand.
捍卫者的名字
The champion's name.
说出来
Say it.
听着  没有冒犯  先生
Look, no offense, mister,
但我不认为这些事情是你最感兴趣的
but I don't think these things have your best interest at heart.
别听这个孩子的话
Don't listen to this child.
把他推过去
Take the staff.
握住它说捍卫者的名字
Hold it and say the champion's name.
他们在利用你
They're using you.
你得看看 他们在利用你
You have to see that. That they are using you.
说出你的名字
Say your name.
他的名字…
His name...
是斯帕克芬格船长
is Captain Sparklefingers.
我们要继续扔东西
And we're gonna keep throwing things
在你又大又胖又丑的头上
at your big, fat, ugly ass head
直到你放了我们的弟弟
until you let our brother go.
孩子  我很高兴没有 把蝙蝠镖卖掉
Boy, am I glad I didn't sell that batarang.
佩德罗  那是台灯吗
Pedro, is that a lamp?
-这是一个丑陋的 -快点  快点  快点
- It's an ugly one. - Come on, come on, come on.
伙计们  我很感激 想  我真的想
Guys, I appreciate the thought, I really do.
但我不认为你 武器会有帮助的
But I don't think your weapons are gonna help.
你现在可以把它们放下了
You can put 'em down now.
门就在这里
The door was right here.
比利  我们怎么样 离开这里
Billy, how do we get out of here?
什么  你认为我知道 我不知道
What, you think I know? I don't know.
这边
This way!
走走走走  和达拉一起走 干得好  达拉
Go, go, go, go, go with Darla. Good job, Darla!
走  走  走  走
Go, go, go, go!
孩子们
Kids?
为什么打开
Why is this open?
弗莱迪
Freddy?
玛丽
Mary?
弗雷迪  弗雷迪  跟上
Freddy, Freddy, keep up.
达拉  呆在前面
Darla, stay in front.
我们得快点
We gotta hurry.
-哇 -哇
- Whoa. - Whoa.
这么多门
So many doors.
其中之一必须是 一条出路  对吗
One of these has to be a way out, right?
是的  我希望如此
Yeah, I would hope so.
不是这个
Not this one.
好了  别再开门了
Okay, no more doors.
大家别再开门了
Nobody open any more doors.
比利 我们该怎么办
Come on, Billy, what are we gonna do?
达拉  我不知道
Darla, I don't know.
比利  是的  你知道 只是想想而已
Billy, yes, you do, just-just think.
上次你怎么出去的
How'd you get out last time?
嗯  呃  我——上次我 想到了地铁
Well, uh, l-last time I thought about the subway
我在地铁上
and I was on the subway.
比利  看 想想地铁
Then Billy, look, think about the subway.
想想任何地方 除了这里  好吗
Think about any place except for here, okay?
快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on.
你为什么遮住我的眼睛
Why are you covering my eyes?
搞什么？  这是你第一个想到的地方？哇！
Really? This is the first place you think of? Wow!
不客气
You're welcome.
为什么我看不见里面是什么
Why can't I see what's inside?
你还不够大
You are not old enough.
年龄足够大就能知道那很棒的音乐了
Old enough to know that was great music.
不是我的事
Not my thing.
弗莱迪在哪里
Where's Freddy?
是的  你也是  斯瑞拉查  嘿
Yeah, you too, Sriracha, hey,
祝你圣诞快乐
have a holly, jolly Christmas.
弗雷迪  你在干什么
Freddy, what are you doing?
啊  是好人
Ah, it's nice people.
-漂亮的人…… 走吧  -那是闪光的吗
- Nice pe...? Come on. - Is that glitter?
它们闪闪发光 我能拿到闪光片吗
They have glitter. Can I get glitter?
-不  不是他们的  拜托
- No, not from them. - Please?
走  走  走  走 大家快走
Go, go, go, go! Everybody go!
弗雷迪  弗雷迪  弗雷迪
Freddy, Freddy, Freddy.
一  二  三 紧紧抓住我
One, two, three, hold onto me.
狂欢节  走  走  走 玛丽  走
Carnival. Go, go, go. Mary, go.
去吧  快点  佩德罗
Go. Come on, Pedro.
来吧
Come on.
走路  保持冷静  动作自然点
Walk, just be cool, act naturally,
就像孩子们在嘉年华里自然地玩一样
like kids naturally act in a carnival.
-他不会找你的…那是他吗
- He's not gonna look for you... - Is that him?
哦  天哪  伙计们
Oh, my God, guys.
嘿  超能男孩
Hey, Powerboy.
他是个模仿者  好吗
He's an impersonator, okay?
我是个模仿者 我是我自己的假象
I'm an impersonator. I'm a fake version of myself.
不要拍照…
Don't take pictures...
沙赞
Shazam!
嘿  他去哪儿了
Hey, where'd he go?
哦  伙计  哦  伙计 我刚刚吐到了一个婴儿
Oh, man, oh, man, I just spit on a baby!
哟  那是什么
Yo, what is that?
捍卫者
Champion!
你不配得到那个名字
You don't deserve that name.
躲在无辜的人后面  他们现在要死了
Hiding behind innocent people who will now die.
因为在内心深处  你 还是个害怕的小男孩
Because deep down, you're still just a scared, little boy.
哦  不
Oh, no.
跑
Run!
-我们该怎么办  我们该怎么办 -坚持住
- What do we do? What do we do? - Hold on!
-什么  -你个白痴
- To what? - The bar, you idiot!
你想让我成为英雄
Well, you wanted me to be a hero.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
好吧  不  那个老家伙在上面
Okay, no. Old guy's up there
拥有精神分裂的人
harboring multiple spiritual entities,
另外  我是说  他有 和你一样的力量
plus, I mean, he has the same powers as you,
另外  你知道  他知道他在做什么
plus, you know, a-and he knows what he's doing,
另外  你是我最好的朋友 我不想你死
plus, you're my best friend, I don't want you to die.
如果是超级英雄 无法拯救他的家人
If a superhero can't save his family,
他就不是什么英雄
he's not much of a hero.
这是一个很好的流行语
That was a decent catchphrase.
沙赞
Shazam!
现在让我们再来一次
Now let's try this again.
或者再试一次
Or try that again.
比利  小心
Billy, look out!
激光眼
Laser eyes?
伙计们  他有激光眼
Guys, he's got laser eyes!
你的目标太差了  糟透了
Too bad your aim sucks balls!
他的能量矩阵
His power matrix.
他的什么
His what what?
当恶魔们离开的时候 他的眼睛失去了力量
When the demon guys leave his eye, he loses his powers.
这就是为什么蝙蝠镖伤了他
That's why the batarang hurt him.
嘿  过来
Hey, over here!
你在干什么
W-What are you doing?
相信我  分而治之
Trust me. Divide and conquer.
我们把罪与眼分开  他就只是个普通老人
We separate the sins from the eye, and he's just an old man.
把这些杂碎都抓起来
Gather the mutts.
来  拿着它 拿着  这是给你的
Here, take it. Take it, it's for you.
紧紧抓住它
Hold it tight.
闭上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
一切都会好起来的 好吗？
Everything's gonna be okay. Okay?
好的
Okay.
起来
Get up.
沙赞
Shazam!
游戏结束了  孩子
Playtime's over, boy.
你的朋友不能 再帮你一把
Your friends can't help you anymore.
嘿
Hey!
沙赞
Shazam!
好把戏
Nice trick.
引人注意的
Catchy.
一个简单的词
One simple word.
我有更好的技巧
I have a better trick.
四个字
Four words.
杀了那个小女孩
Kill the little girl.
-不  拜托 -不
- No, please! - No!
住手
Stop!
比利  他的眼睛里还有一个恶魔
Billy, there's one more demon guy in his eye!
你只要把它从他脸上撕下来…
You gotta just rip it out of his face...
这就是他获得力量的方法
It's where he gets his power.
伸手去碰他
Reach for it.
我谅你也不敢
I dare you.
明智的决定
Wise decision.
把手放在法杖上
Hands on the staff.
比利  不要这么做  比利
Billy, don't do this. Billy!
-比利 -别这样  比利
- Billy! - Don't do it, Billy!
说出我的名字
Say my name
所以我的力量就会赋予你
so my power may flow through you.
我向你敞开心扉
Billy Batson I open my heart to you, Billy Batson.
这样做
And in so doing,
选择你作为捍卫者
choose you as champion.
用你的心 释放你最大的力量
With your heart, unlock your greatest power.
我兄弟姐妹的王位都在等着呢
The thrones of our brothers and sisters await!
所有人都握住法杖
All hands on deck.
说出我的名字
Say my name.
比利
Billy!
不  不是我的名字  不
No, not my name. No.
说出我说的变成这个人的名字
Say the name that I say to turn into this guy.
沙赞
Shazam!
伙计们
Guys.
发生什么事了
What's happening?
我会飞
I can fly!
伙计们
Guys.
看看这些肌肉
Check out these guns.
不
No.
不可能
It's not possible!
天哪  先生  对不起  我拿走了你的法杖
Gee whiz, mister. Sorry I took your game.
你想要回来吗
You want it back?
伙计们  我不喜欢暴力
Guys, I don't believe in violence,
但我觉得我们应该狠狠地踢这家伙的屁股
but I think we should kick this guy's butt, like, really hard.
伙计们  我想 我真的可以移动的
Guys, I think I can move really
很快
fast.
超高速
Hyperspeed!
确认无误
Check!
比利
Billy!
眼睛
The eye.
留神
Look out!
哇
Whoa!
什么
What?
你差点把我炸了
You almost exploded me!
伙计  我学过了 战斗技巧
Dude, I've studied the fighting techniques
每一个超级英雄
of every single superhero.
你有什么
What do you got?
好吧  那太可怕了
Well, that's terrifying.
够了  孩子
Enough games, boy.
你认为一群孩子能…
You think a pack of children can...
等等  什么
Wait, what?!
你会乞求宽恕的
You will beg for mercy
当我饱餐你的心的时候
as I feast on your heart.
慢…
Slow...
你在做什么大坏蛋
Are you making some big, evil guy
现在说话还是什么
speech right now or something?
你现在离我一英里远
You're like, a mile away from me right now.
有汽车和卡车…
There's cars and trucks...
我将掌握全世界…
I will have the world eating out of the palm of my hand...
我只看到嘴在动 我听不到任何…
All I see is mouth moving. I don't hear any...
只有我
Only I
有能力释放…
have the power to unleash...
哦  不管怎样  去死吧
Oh, whatever, screw it.
哦  天哪  那些人
Oh, my gosh, those people!
你好
Hi!
我抓到你了
I caught you!
我得到了它
I got it!
我撑住它了
哦  天哪  我明白了
Oh, my God, I do got it.
你不会相信的
You're not gonna believe this,
但实际上你是我第一个打过的恶棍
but you're actually the first villain I've ever fought.
对我来说  这是一笔巨大的买卖
It's, like, kind of a huge deal for me.
谁来帮帮我
Somebody help!
哈多梗
Hadouken!
你好
Hi!
哇  真的是你
Wow, it's really you.
我叫达拉  我一直都很好
My name is Darla and I've been really good!
什么
What?
哦  见鬼
Oh, crap.
不  不  不  不 不  不
No, no, no, no. No, no!
哦  天哪
Oh, my God!
我要给你穿手提箱内裤!
I'm giving you suitcase wedgies!
所以这是关于你的 七宗罪  对吧
So this is about your Seven Deadly Sins, right?
我是说  我数学从来就不是很好  但是…
I mean, I've never been great at math, but uh...
愤怒的大家伙  那是愤怒  是吗
The big, angry one, that's Wrath, yeah?
然后是暴饮暴食
And then Gluttony, obvi.
骄傲
Pride.
贪婪和懒惰  欲望  谁
Greed and Sloth, Lust, who
老实说，我还以为会更厉害呢。
I thought was gonna be way hotter, if I'm being honest.
但只有六个  那…幸运数字七在哪里
But that's only six. Where's... Where's lucky number seven?
小家伙在哪里  嫉妒在哪里
Where's little man? Where's Envy?
他只是害怕我和我的家人  因为我们太棒了吗
Is he just scared of me and my family 'cause we're so awesome?
因为我明白了
'Cause I get that.
就像  其他的罪  他们会出来战斗
Like, the other sins, they get to come out and fight
因为它们又大又壮又可怕
'cause they're big and strong and scary.
但嫉妒
But Envy,
他只是个小矮子
he's just a runt.
这就是为什么 所有其他的罪
And that's why all the other sins
从不邀请他 出去玩  伙计
never invite him out to play, man.
因为他们都知道谁会赢
'Cause they all know who'd win.
它并不强
And it's not weak,
无用的  丑陋的
worthless, ugly
嫉妒
Envy.
不
No!
抓住了
Gotcha.
沙赞
Shazam!
准备好围捕你的朋友了吗
Ready to go round up your buddies?
不
No.
No!
这是关于力量的事情
Here's the thing about power.
多好的力量
What good's power
如果你没有人和你分享
if you got nobody to share it with?
- 好样的 哒哒
- Nice. - Ta-da.
太恶心了
That's disgusting.
致命性
Fatality.
我听到了声音
I got the voice.
那是什么
What's that?
我能得到我想要的任何东西吗
I can have anything I've ever wanted?
比利  不
Billy, no.
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no!
-你应该看看你自己  -这不好笑
- You should hear yourself. - That's not funny.
什么  你认为我会把一个恶魔球放在我的头上？
What, you think I'm gonna put a demon ball in my head?
太恶心了
That's disgusting.
-这不好笑  -很有趣  你让我走了
- It's not funny. - Pretty funny. You got me going.
伙计们  伙计们
Uh, guys, guys.
什么
What?
哦  嘿
Oh, hey.
哦  哇
Oh, wow.
-哦 -哦
- Oh. - Oh.
好吧  我们做到了
All right, we did it!
-哇 -好吧  是啊
- Whoo! - All right! Yeah!
谢谢您
Thank you!
我们做到了
We did it!
是的  你们都很安全 没有危险了
Yeah, you guys are all safe. There's no more danger.
你确定这样行吗
You sure this is gonna work?
告诉你
Told ya.
你们知道 这是什么地方  对吧
You guys know what this place is, right?
一个黑暗  鬼魂出没的洞穴 有恶魔雕像
A dark, haunted cave with demon statues.
是的  但是…
Well, yes, but also...
藏身处
Lair!
我们有个藏身处
We got a lair!
藏身处
Lair.
-莱尔 -我们有一个藏身处
- Lair. - We got a lair.
什么是藏身处
What's a lair?
多亏了六个超级英雄
And thanks to six superheroes,
citizens are back in their homes
和他们的家人安全
safe again with their families.
这里有目击者对事件的描述…
And here with an eyewitness account of the events...
太疯狂了  伙计
It was f***ing crazy, man!
来自地狱的生物
Creatures from f***ing hell!
闪电从每个人的身上发出
Lightning coming out of everyone's f***ing everything.
这可不酷  伙计
And that is not f***ing cool, man!
我受够了
I'm tired of it.
这是
<i>♪ This will be ♪</i>
永恒的爱
<i>♪ An everlasting love ♪</i>
伙计们
Guys,
所有人都把手放上来
all hands on deck.
哦
Oh!
等等
W-W-WOW W-W-W-Wait!
Wait.
谢谢你的食物
Thank you for this food.
感谢你今天的到来
Thank you for this day.
谢谢你的家人
Thank you for this family.
我想也许 这次我会留下来
I thought maybe this time I'd stay.
我是说 也许
I mean, after all,
我到家了
I'm home.
不
Nope.
可以
Okay.
你在干什么
What are you doin'?
等待你想象中的永远的最好的朋友出现？
Waiting for your imaginary BFF to show up?
你们在这里干什么
What are you guys doing here?
好吧  我们和你一起吃午饭
Well, we're having lunch with you.
但你们有不同的午餐时间
But you guys have different lunch periods.
嗯  我们做了一个非常特别的安排
Well, we made a very special arrangement.
达拉  怎么了
Darla, what's going on?
你为什么问我
Why are you asking me?
弗雷迪·弗里曼  弗雷迪·弗里曼
Freddy Freeman Freddy Freeman!
这个家伙…
This guy...
教会了我所有关于成为超级英雄的知识
taught me everything I know about being a dope superhero.
这是真事  你应该得到一些指导
True story, you should get some pointers
他怎么了
from him. What's goin' on,
我世界上最好的朋友
my best bud... in the whole world?
还有我第一次见到的新朋友
And also new kids that I'm meeting for the first time
不过这看起来很酷？
but seem very cool?
嗯哼
Uh... huh,
我邀请了另一个朋友  希望他准备好了
I invited another friend, I hope that's okay.
啊！
Huh!
字幕制作  热心群里的人
english subs by enwansix